Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show Star shine is alright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands, whisper what
You know?
Here we go, here we go.
Here we go.
Enjoy the ride.
That's enough.
Here we go.
Thank you guys.
We're coming back.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Hey guys, what's up? Sorry, but I just wanted to I think it's a good introduction
It's all good. I was just letting you know she didn't show any food or anything
Oh, yeah, you want to start over because you're 12 hour mark. I saw a little I might as well just a little tiny little
Nipslip. Oh, that was her tattoo. Oh, okay
Sorry, I promise she didn't I was trust me. I was looking for some nipple and she didn't show none. Okay
She doesn't have nice movies though. What is this? What is Alex doing? Shout out to all the girls with nice movies. What is that Alex?
What is that? What is that? Oh, you're the casino?
Alex, what are you doing walking around the casino? I thought you were right up to switch areas because my wife
I keep cutting when I come on the side of the house
This is a so it's Alex for sure
He's in a casino. Oh
Hey everybody in chat welcome back. We have a let's see. I'll put the banner back up. Thank you. You've talked your ish
Responsing this panel until 1 30 a.m. It's 11 11 right now, Los Angeles
Until 1 30 a.m. So that's 11 12 12 12 like two and a half hours
And then we have another one two after that one. Well, probably tomorrow
A lot of energy. Yeah, whatever. It's fine. Whenever I get money tonight or tomorrow, but I got one prepaid
Yes, thank you so much. And if I am tomorrow wait till I'm here tomorrow, please cuz I have to work of course, of course
Well congratulations Alex
10 grays, I just want 10 grays and motherfuckers, ha, ha, ha.
It's in his house, he didn't win the next one, y'all.
Ah!
Alex, Alex, you know that, right?
Alex, get a buck, 20 bucks.
They borrowed 20 bucks, Alex?
I'm just kidding.
Alex.
Wow Alex
The money just comes out of the machine like that Alex oh, yeah, the money just like you know
They just throw a hundred dollar bills out of the machine
That's right. That's how they work in the casino, right? They come just gonna have the hundred dollar bills on the truck
Yes, sure. Whatever go
What happened?
Where's everybody?
I'm here. Oh, wait, there's 40 people already in the chat. Wow. It's only been eight minutes. That's awesome. Hey, what's up guys?
Hey, I'm here
Yeah, I think Alex has he bought a bunch of fake money on Amazon and then he like just put throws it around like he's like
Christa like yeah, that's not that wasn't he didn't he's at his home. It doesn't come out of the machine like that
What is he?
Is he has a machine? He does have a room that looks a lot like a casino, but yeah, it does kind of look like a house
You can you can buy those my son has a couple of those
Alex nice try Alex, and they're not fooling in here. Thank you
That was a very elaborate hoax
Wow, look at this. I have one of these I have apples and I can you hear me psyche? Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Okay, I lost my blood I'm looking for what it's showing all the titties
Well, it looks like I'm just gonna have to roll another one. I don't know what I'd do with my blunt. I lost it.
Say hi, Psyche!
What do you mean? Look at there.
You say hi?
What are you looking for? You say hi to Psyche?
There's my I think I think I'm smart you so I get either you're muted or I'm can't you can't hear me one of the
I'm sorry. I mean I was muted. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Oh, okay. I'm sorry. I was I was on mute
Let me see I'm trying to
Hi, baby, what a gorgeous kitty cat you she runs me my Lola
I know she doesn't like that her and Lola would be sisters freaky for Saturday. That's what we need. Yeah shadow shadow work Saturday
That's what it was. That was a shadow work. All right, Chris. Are you Chris is there? Yeah, that's me
Okay, what's up, dude?
I'm good. I'm good. So I'm a spunky
Yes
that's okay it's alright to act up every now and then yes you weren't alone so
that makes it good there was a bunch of us doing it yeah it was kind of it was
kind of pretty pretty pretty great
I think I really
The psyche angels all have nice tits
You know what second ages they do I have the best-looking like the best-looking audience
I mean, you know, I'm great-looking male men and women too and then um, but uh, the psyches angels we reached 101
Psyche's Angels today. There's 101 members.
It's a little easy. It's okay. I was wilding, but whatever.
Alright, baby. I donated a hundredth one, so now I can have more emojis.
I'm going to have an emoji. I'm going to do a beta emoji, I think.
And then maybe I'll do something. I don't know. I'm just kidding.
I don't know. I don't know. I did put some, I did a grandma emoji.
I put like an old lady with like that. I don't know. I just put a grandma.
I'm like, I don't know if you can see them through the streamer though. I've seen on the screen
Who is big rod? I don't even know him. I've never seen him before and he's wild and big Rob
Is a big robber big Robin big rod big rod is loses mine that I'm naked. Oh
Big ride, I don't know. Some of these guys are just a little bit
Do you guys are y'all sure y'all like women some of y'all because you know, we were having fun. What's this?
Y'all got problem with titties?
Y'all want to see nut sacks instead? I get it, but sorry it was boobs. I don't like
I don't like nut sacks. I can read some nut sacks. Do you want to see that?
No, I don't want to see button that sex, please. Okay, hold on. Yeah, I look like alien brains. They don't look cute
There's nothing about yeah, they are they are alien brains. Oh, and this is what is this one? I don't know. Oh, yeah
This is my tattoo right now. He loves my titties. That's my tattoo. You guys see my tattoo right there
They're one of the icons nasty. I don't know it's on the screen. It's my tattoo
Little cat said okay, and what else I have I put uh the skull I changed I have the evil eye thing
I mean guys you have a suggestion. I have a troll thing. I have more I have more stuff too man
I'm gonna put more stuff on there
Vampire now
You can spam the chat with all these emojis if you want members, okay
Yes
Oh
I love it
Okay. Hey easy cameras on he's Sam and a big hold on me. I can't see big broad. Okay, Lord Bader
Solid wild German lady. Welcome
Lord Bader Jamie's Cowboys. Oh my god, a lot of people here. Welcome everybody Baldwin baby. I had all members
Yeah, 101 members guys
When we were showing our boobies his heart was his chest was hurting. Oh my god, right? Well, my my uh, you know
Oh, he wasn't even up yet. Well, he was in the chair, right? I
Was yep, I was worried about there would be a nip slip, but there wasn't I guess
I held that shit hard to thank you. I would never I would never perform on you
The floating diamond which showed her nipples like three times and that I was like and they're not like the nicest nipple
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but it's like I mean it's like kind of like
They're like dark and they're like kind of big
She's on the chat. Oh my god, they were dark and big
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
What apps
Never mind sir, I'm sorry
As long as they match the boom
Absolutely
Because I got I got big titties and I got big areolas. I will explain you what small small nip. You know me
I got small nipples, but my areolas big. I
Love you sort of them
Yeah, I'm sort of diving like actually they was like rubbing on a like a balloon for under her dress
It was like a and then I think I got in trouble for that video I deleted but then she did flash
But I stuck her under like this like the text right there
So I don't know if anybody saw anything, but she did a I've seen her boobs several times though
Whoo
I feel like I'm a Mardi Gras or Howard Stern had
We should all get a discount on sponsoring on a panel
Maybe I can add beads to the merch. I'll try to add some beads and we can have and I'll add some like you know
Your snickers should be a set of beads. Yeah. Oh, yeah, we can do I can do that on t-shirts, too
I'll put the beads. I'll put like don't forget to make a psychies
Officials say official psychies angels freak offs. Yeah, sure t-shirt t-shirt. Yeah, I'll make one. Yeah. Yeah, I'll make one for the
psychies angels, yep
They only I'll have to figure out how only members all his ankles are hot and got nice racks
Yep, see look they look like it. Yeah look like this
See there we are Chris Oh
A couple more of us we've got to get at it I like that I like that and then and then the men I want that on a black teacher
I'm gonna know there's there's a man right there. Here's all the men in the chat
Yeah, okay. Yeah, look at day one right behind. Yeah.
Can I ask you a question? Yes. Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit. That was that Josephie.
That was Bita and Kate.
He kicked out whatever happened with that.
Who is who kicked out?
Oh, who?
This rat bitch that we all don't like.
Uh-uh, no, the mic from a different community. Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you were talking. Okay
Hey, flirty
Not me and flirty ain't had no we've been arguing
sure
Well flirty if you mean if you if you get to promise flirty if you wouldn't if you want to come back out
You have to like promise you never gonna ever porn bomb again. She I think she's gotten sober, you know, so I think that might be better
for
Imagine being blocked, Christine,
and the reason I see your comments is because the screen,
oh yeah, she's even blocking people, okay, whatever.
Nobody, sorry.
So, yeah, so I think Janet was pretty,
I didn't really like the appearance today,
like I probably, it was an open panel,
and so I had, I let people, I was letting people on,
and maybe that was like a little bit,
but we didn't have a fun time talking to her at the beginning,
You know, hey, I'm gonna let you know now. I'll come up here and sponsor a panel every single time
She's up here just to come up and talk shit to that bitch
Well, it was it was kind of entertaining it was like I think the panel's right
I don't like everyone's really like everyone's really liking it the that the panel today though
It was kind of fun. So if the chat was like, yeah, they loved it
So I was like, hey, it's like if people are loving it then even if it's like bad, it's good, you know
They're loving this, I hear.
Yay, I'm the, what the fuck was she like, Janet?
I agree, but fuck them.
What'd she say?
I have a short, I have a short term memory.
Like, I don't really remember.
Like, I've registered to remember, like, she said,
oh, he's like, maybe like, you know,
she said I'm on drugs or my,
I don't know, my nails are dirty or something.
That's what everyone has said, you know?
Is there really a logic?
She said your nails are dirty, you're a drug addict,
you're a scammer, she said all kinds of shit.
That's why I don't like that, but she's fake as fuck.
She talks shit about everybody.
She talks shit about Alex, she talks about me, you,
everybody.
just everybody is over here she's talking shit and then she blocks through everybody from her chat
and i didn't even say nothing to her except for that bird has bronze bird has the right to reply
when she's talking shit she felt some type of white so i dragged that fucking nasty ass looking
Everybody go and I don't know that either are they so backstage with somebody is there there's so backstage with Marcy
Oh, hey Marcy. Oh, yeah everyone that I'm just kidding. I was of course
I see there could be more rumors of like more freak office. Here we go. There you go 10%
Yeah, there's no freak officer go on. I
Left before I saw anything. I don't know if they showed anything
Let's
See big rod. Okay. Oh, yeah, I don't talk about yeah, Christine's holding it down in the chat. It's a great mod
Thank you. It's not really flashing when flirty does it
He said some foul shit about you Jansk gross. Let me see
She says something about spreading AIDS. Oh my god
That's not very nice. She I don't I don't I'm not even I don't sleep with anybody let alone. That's crazy. Hold on here
Alex that was real money, bro. That was real money. Where are you the kids people so broken that you can't buy fake money on Amazon?
That's a hundred percent fact, but that was real money
Yeah, I know it hurts you
I know it hurts you broke bitch that I can throw money around like that
You're not
You're not impressing anybody
Anybody Alex people that talk about you think you're the only one that has fucking money you dumb fuck
People are talking about money like this. He's been spanked sponsor in the fucking panels for two days, bitch. Go fuck yourself
Exactly hey Marcy
Marcy in the chat
Yeah, I mean Alex and don't call people don't these are beautiful ladies wait
What are you talking people names for and then you're like who cares about money that you're talking here?
You're acting like some kind of rapper that is like just really doesn't care about money
It's like it's really an attractive when people talk about money like that like oh I have so much
You know you don't listen talk about like that. It's like ridiculous. Okay. No one's impressed panel link stream yard
Yes, thank you. Are you gonna pin that? Okay. Thank you so much, Christine. Let's see
And I don't think perfect
There you
Okay
Chris, how are you tonight? This is Chris cab. How are you? Yeah? Yeah, I'm good. I'm good
Dylan
Where abouts is Chris?
I'm in blood. He's from my place. Oh, okay. Okay, so that's like you know who Lisa Jordana is
It's a Jordana. Yeah, you remember you I think we've seen her before all right Chris
She's the she's a chick. She'd be doing all kinds of crazy shit. I feel like I've showed her to you before
I'll show I'll send you her thing
Thank you
Okay, awesome. He likes her
I haven't been there for a few weeks, so I just like been so focused so much away. Are you rolling your eyes Lord Bader?
Yeah, anyway, she's in Florida. She's in like a del Rey
the West Palm Beach and my
Boca we're talking about she's nice by Nikola. Okay. Hey, that's part of the house. I'm gonna have to switch to the other room
It's part of the house my internet key
And
She out she drives around and here she has perfect reception for the for internet
But then as soon as she goes to certain places like restaurants, it doesn't have any connections. She has to go inside for the Wi-Fi
I don't get that. I don't understand why I
Don't know and run. Okay 10% okay. I need to fix my fucking tablet. I see not charging
Yeah, okay, anyway, would anybody like a card or two?
Anybody in the check one just give me there. Okay summer. Okay, let me see. I'll do the
If you found a blunt, we believe that
I'm gonna pull from this alien alien deck. This is alien dick. I just got
That's really cool. Oh
Here's there's obviously gonna be a really cute. Oops shit
Okay, summer
Cute okay
Summer ace of cups you're gonna be handed something that's gonna make you very very happy and look at it's pretty interesting
There's all these aliens around it and there's I
This cup if there's like it's some kind of consciousness in it people are watching you too ace of cups
You're gonna be handed something that will make you very happy overflow your cup overflow. Oh
Alex is a
playing at the backstage, okay.
So then we have, oh, and we've got another ace.
You've got two aces, ace of swords here.
You have this ability to,
actually you're receiving the truth with this ace of sword.
So I think it's by, you know, being in nature,
just like being enlightened, see this person's enlightened.
Ace of swords means the truth.
You can know the truth about something,
you are enlightened about something.
And, oh, okay, then we have the two of swords.
This is like a kind of tunnel vision card.
Also looks like there's two paths you can go.
You also might not be seeing the whole picture.
It might be being blocked by those two people.
I'm gonna put one more card.
Words of advice for summer, please.
Three of wands work together with a few other people.
Look at, that looks like 33 or something like that.
We're three of three of wands. It's like you're gonna have more power
putting your putting your energies together
You know other people on some ground a girl
So it looks like you do work with other people and you're do you work with other people in your outreach?
Or do you are you totally I do and I have a big federal court case coming up on Monday?
And so if that's any sign of what you're saying
You just said you just said that I've hold the justice card. This is it. Oh, wow
Look at that
Right. Oh my god. I hope you're right. It's like yes. Oh, this is right
Yeah, and so I think if I come back Monday and give you a big kiss, you'll know why
Okay, well, it looks like you know, it looks like you've got you have the advantage in this court case and
You know, it's just like just tell the truth and
Um, and then I think the justice will be served in the upright. So it looks good for you. Hey vinyl peeled
I try to drop and give the panels on I see that are always positive and good conversation
I haven't popped up yet, but you've watched a vinyl. Thank you so much. I appreciate that so much. You're awesome
Thank you vinyl
Guys are awesome. I love you guys
Yeah, that's that's that makes me I guess I was really so I got some bad news because the prosecutor went in and said they only want one day
And a hundred dollar fine for an 11 somebody which is crazy, right?
And so but the judge gets the last say and our courts at the sentencing of Monday, so we'll find out what happens
Nine o'clock in the morning, baby
Wow, I wish you good luck and it looks like the car during an indication looks like it's gonna go pretty well, so
Yeah, I was worrying about it at first, but then I was like, you know what, worry if I don't do anything
I'm just gonna have faith that it's gonna be the way it needs to be
Yeah
That's what I mean. I try to do that too with life. It's like because it's like
If you can't if something is like if you have no control over it, why worry about it? You don't have to worry about it at all
It's like you have it's like so it's like that's kind of like that prayer. What's that prayer? It's like give me the
Strength to see what about me? I can't change what I can't change and then the
Wisdoms know the difference and things like that, right?
Serenity prayer or something like that. Let's see Christina and Katrina and Christina or Christina still up
Where's Gotti, poor, okay, so I don't know what Slayer's saying.
Okay, well, anyway, if anyone,
Marcy, there's an ex Howard Stern writer turned the streamer.
Oh, Marcy, she, hold on, yeah,
at least in Jordana, yes, she was a writer, right?
Where Sweep Pea, she wasn't kind of a,
you know, she was kind of mad this morning,
but she comes back once in a while,
she always comes back.
She would, sometimes she gets mad if I don't see her
and say hi to her, but I miss a lot of the chat comments.
Oh
So I
Alright Chris, so I got this cool watch psyche. I feel like an expected gadget. So I got this watch
So I haven't messed with it yet
But it's a whoo. It's a really nice watch, right? I gotta put it still together, right? But the cool thing about this watch
Every court look at that. Oh
Perfect. Oh shit, you're
You heard hey Chris. I got it. You already know what this is for
So I'm I'm not gonna say on here
Hold on is anybody up here besides us if I write something in the back
No, like Alex is here. So yeah
Okay, thank you so so much
Yeah, she was also yes, that's yeah person's right about uh, yeah, that's at least at least they're talking about
Yeah, Christie. Okay, so my Chris. What is your astrological sign?
Yeah, it's all about the last thing. Oh, I was I was oh your capricorn. Okay. What do you have a married or something?
Are you married?
No, no, you're not okay young the girlfriend are married. How about you crucible? What's your sign?
Crucible
Ghost you sponsored the panel the you sponsored the panel the other night, but you didn't send me a cash up for it
So, but I just wanted to like let you know if I appreciate I will I said, oh
Well, I said I was gonna give you money. Yeah
I said promise that you'll I said I was starting to charge for the panel the open do open start open panels
And you said I want to come on and I say can you give me your promise as a man that you'll pay me?
And you said yes, I promise and then you came up and I would never
Yes, you have you said you're gonna buy pay for half my fish tacos once and you never did that either
Yeah, so but if you'd like to I mean, I would appreciate that it's like I don't be man of your word because I did let you on it
When I had the panel closed the other night, so you know, and then you know every people have I'm never
But I'm not gonna ever like let somebody pay on credit again
I guess that's not the best way to do that because I mean unless it was like summer, you know, but it's like
Because why was it?
Why what why was the panel closed?
The panels closed because I'm I'm gonna begin to do for I'm gonna I'll do one-on-one
Talks with people, you know, and I not and I'll be like, you know
I'll just bring the people on but if there's open panels
Because like they get they take it take a lot of time sometimes and they can get like, you know a little bit
Crazy and I want them to be sponsored. So but I also give the advertisement for it. So I will like um
I will put your banner up to if you send it out and I don't know whatever you want to advertise if you want
Or put on the banner. I'll put for right now Christine sponsor in it, right? Yeah
Yeah, I would do it. I would do it when it when there's nobody when there's nobody sponsoring one
But Christine corresponds with this channel this panel. Yeah, you gotta put her name on there
You didn't put her name there. It's there. It's there. It's there. She said to put your talk. We should oh, she has to put your talk
You should talk. Oh, I see. I see. I see. I see
Say that well my bad, dude. I didn't know
OK, well, I thought that's all you did.
Well, I just kind of modified it because some of the panels
have been getting really time-consuming.
OK, that's OK.
That's cool.
So, that means when you sponsor a panel, the burden of proof could be on everybody.
Yeah, well, it's not a, it's not a, it's not a, it's not a, it's not a, the person, the person that,
also the person that sponsors the panel does not get, uh, does not connect, they cannot get
kicked off their, their, uh, the panel they sponsor, so no, so that they're like immune to that.
I did hear that earlier because I was listening to you guys earlier.
Plus, plus, plus I'll put up their banner.
Whatever they want me to put on the banner and thank you thank them for so that's advertising and hopefully people will whatever they want
Yeah, whatever you want as long as it's not against the TOS, you know, you can put whatever and also just break the TOS
Otherwise, that's fine. Everything's good
And I'll be fine and I'll also be here more like and not like disappear and stuff as much because I want to
You know, I want to make sure I participate to
I think it will be more on top ticket and more people people appreciate here we go
I think I think I just will be sure I this wasn't drunk the other night
And you tried to explain that to me, and I just wasn't all the way there you might have been drunk
But you
Was she acting like
No, you were just drunk and that's the only time you disrespect and call us names is when you're drunk. How much does he owe you?
That's not true
Ten bucks. Yeah, you don't you don't you don't call you don't call us bitches and shit much or trash you talk shit
But you don't everybody goes family money. I do say dumb guy. I can pay for what pay money for what?
Okay, I won't
That's not cool. Yeah, it's an example for motherfuckers like that. Yeah, I know it's like, you know
He's kind of laughing about I don't like I he didn't promise and it's like and then he like not
Don't welch on that shit, man. Yeah
You're doing it left and right, you know
Yeah, I can't do so fun like credit
This is serious shit
Yeah, and yeah, that's part of it. It's like I wanted the panel to be kind of taken more seriously too some people will maybe
Okay, Justin is talking shit to me put him on I'll take care of him. No, he is like he said
He wants me to tell all of you that we're broken up
Aldi
Who knows where we are broken up and then he is gonna go talk to Carmel
What who's Carmell is
the Jewish woman the Jewish woman and
Why
He's done. He's so mad
He's done with you. Yeah, it's done with me. All right good. Fuck it. I'll be over there
And he's breaking up breaking up with you to come see with me. He's done
Fuck them I'll move in
I knew he was trouble from the moment. I'll break up with my girl, and I'll move in with you
Two weeks God you were the one me and you how long have you guys been together spunky?
He's trippin, dude. Don't get over yourself. Yeah. Yeah, he's not gonna find anything better than you
Oh, we were all up here having a good time. He wasn't when you weren't doing anything for
What's he mad about
But you know
We were all showing our boobs with the tattoo all the boobs stuff
She showed her dad. She showed her tattoo like she has a tattoo there big fucking big deal
What what's the point of her having a tattoo if she's not gonna show it off?
She covered her fucking nipples like it over. It's not being secured. Don't worry Mel. Don't worry
So Alex is backstage. What do you think Alex? Yeah, he'll be over at student spot. Don't worry
I'm at his house right now.
No, no, no, hold on.
So $10 sponsoring a panel buys you immunity?
Okay, yeah, I get that I didn't get the memo. I guess I don't mean to clean the lines on that rule
But for how long for how long for as long as the panelists of usually a couple of two and a half hours about two and a half
Oh, so when so they got immunity as long as the panel because they're sponsored because they give you $10
So if I give you $50, there's no contour immunity
There's nothing
I'm talking a site by the way
Right now, in reality, you will get executed.
Women do not talk while men are talking.
said he didn't want to know you can't come on the panel the rest of the night you dumb fuck
obviously dumb you're gonna do shit but run like you always do when somebody shows up so shut the
fuck up bitch you don't need to have a scheduled a scheduled sponsored calendar
to show everybody because we're sponsored until tomorrow motherfucker so jump in line bitch
yeah i have a uh i have a notebook and i will i will start like you know putting
those things in and people can start their panel when they want to you know and uh
it's this queen's ahead of you use laying motherfucker holler
Everybody's scheduled to run shit schedule their panels. They think they run shit
They don't run a goddamn thing, but they can't even run the fucking stuff. They run their dick in the dirt
That's all they do. They run the fucking mouth shit
Alex yeah
Oh gosh
Love you guys
Everyday I come online to have fun and me having fun just irritates the fuck out of some people and I fuck
It makes my pussy wet. I love it. No, I love it even better
Wonder bonus
Good, that's fun
Do you have fun on the show get fun on here summer? Well, I did not think it didn't make your I always have fun
That's why I'm here
Awesome, I'm a psyche angel. Yeah, yes
Let's see
Fun here, oh yeah fun here absolutely, but sick of the shit
With what Alex
With the duck avatar with the hat
No, I think so. I think that duck avatar is like a purple avatar. I think oh
Now Trevor's nice
He's he's gay, you know, he's very nice. He's one of the only gay people in the show, you know
Besides me. Oh
You know males, okay, so crucible goes
Did you email me Jamie?
Is that what you're saying, babe?
You can't come on you can't you can't come back on the show until you until you pay that because you did promise and so
Dirt cake what the fuck
You know I like dirt cake
Is that what like that cake with like the gummy worms in it? I like that too. No, no dirt cake. Oh
Apparently some southern thing
Okay
Did that tattoo hurt because I was thinking I want to get one right there. I mean my breast
It was the only tattoo of all the tasks you guys
I've had that I was like hang on a minute
And she was like, oh, yeah, I can't not explain. I was like, all right go on with it then
Yeah, I figured my belly my belly kind of hurt. It was it was pretty rough the belly was so I figured right there would be
Because it's all in the same form. I'm gonna get like
area well I have my rib cage done with my side tattoos so I knew what that felt
like but the belly is there's just a lot of nerves especially for a woman I
don't know you know cuz it's yeah it's it's it hurts my when I got man-eater on
my belly it's actually on my live stream I live streamed it and I mean I took
You're beautiful. That's why you're ugly.
You're gorgeous. That's crazy.
I never said that.
Hey, you saw that?
See my shit?
What shit? What?
I should. I should.
I don't think he was here when that happened.
So they showed their boobs.
They're showing their boobs on the stomach.
What did I do?
I didn't do anything. Check it out.
I wasn't here.
Yeah, you missed it.
Say you missed the boobs.
So a major major major there was a yesterday this girl joined my stream and she's joined her. She showed her butthole
Oh, no, she did not. Oh, I think that's a I think
you
Got it. What is that some Asian was actually also an Asian. Oh my god
What color was it? It was crazy yellow black. Oh my god. Oh my god
No, that's interesting. Thank you, babe. I
Don't show us like you ready. I took this for you. Yeah
Ball let's see it. We can't show it on the show, but you can make sure yes
Damn not do it on the stream join my stream join my stream. I'm on do it for boy. Oh
Cheers
Do it on my stream. You could do it on rumble cheers
50 guys, there's like looking for where it is
Can everyone like this dream, please because there's 15 likes and there's 56 people in chat
That'd be so nice if you would like this dream, please do. Thank you so much. Oh those thumbs up buckers. Yeah
It's it's free to just the least thumbs up guys. Thank you
For me, thank you so much, okay
See what can you tell psyche on what?
Where did you send the message Jamie? Oh, yeah
She said something about did you read the chat to keep the panel go?
Is it in discord? I don't know if she maybe she wrote something
I'm not in discord, so I don't know got it. Can you tell the psyche?
Vibration for the tattoo machine. Let me see. Jamie. Well, Jamie's got psyche. Did you read the chat to keep the panel going?
Oh, yeah, I should have kept the panel going or there's a chat to keep the I don't know what you mean to explain
There's a super chat to keep the panel going. Yeah, I was there I think is that summer or what who?
I don't know what she's talking about was there is who's there one the five dollar one
We have been trying to tell you for ten minutes that Jamie said. Oh Jamie also paid for a $10
Don't see I saw it when did you send it this this streamer or the last one somebody sent a $5 one?
Thank you so much. I think a $5 one. Yeah. Oh, yeah, that was maybe that was that one. So that's that'll be yeah
Jamie did send a super Jack Christine said it's um, it's on members. It's on the members
Community Mars
I can check it actually, too
So we'll use we'll use Jamie's and then we'll use mine in the morning. Okay. Oh, yeah, there it is 10 bucks. Yeah
rolling around like
Like a lot here
Thank you so much. I'm sorry. I miss it. I'm sorry. I apologize. I just really didn't see it
I'm sorry. Jamie. It's hard to see when you're up here. Yeah. Love you. Thank you, Jamie. Oh much
Whoa, Jamie's awesome. Thank you so much, Jamie. Yeah, I know and I really want to say a prayer for Jamie
too because she's not she's recovering right now
She was kind of through difficult experience and we want to wish her the fast recovery and healing. Okay, we're covering for what?
She had a car accident. So, you know, yeah, she was in a bad car accident, but
We're sending you lots of good energy. Beautiful. Keep filling. Love you. Hey, Arbiter. Oh, thank you. Thank you
Oh
How I think so much so much how is her condition is that where he came?
He is showing me as penis someone DT is sitting backstage naked. It says
I
Saw penis is now backstage. I'm sorry. Oh
Thank you, thank you so much beautiful
Thank you, crucible. I'll take
Now that we're talking about a car accident. I'll take the opportunity to PSA everybody. Please wear your seatbelts
Ghosts, please wear your seatbelts. It is. Oh, yeah grown
I know but it is literally the only thing that is gonna save your life in the event. I could kill you
Go, all right, so you
But I'm glad you did
It's only thing that's going to save, it's only thing that's going to save you guys, all right, so please wear your seatbelts, you know it's annoying, nobody likes it, but...
You can get a broken neck and be paralyzed with a seat belt.
Yeah, but I would say it's probably more likely that it's going to save,
it's more likely to save you than kill you.
Look, boss, he has a story. Hold on.
My friend's ex was drinking and driving and he missed a turn and he flew off the freeway
and he wasn't wearing his seat belt. And I'd just been telling him like three days before,
like, dude, you're driving when you're faded. Don't be doing that. Call an Uber.
Or at least like where your seatbelt something's gonna happen. I just had a feeling and within a week
He have blown off the freeway was ejected from the vehicle and he passed away
Now you don't kill them. You don't kill them
Being ejected from the yeah drinking and driving but he got ejected from the vehicle and all of his everything was everywhere
Anything but people
is it true, is it true that sometimes we're, sometimes we're people are, yeah
even when you know if your friends are like wasted like that don't let them leave, let them, you know
And then he's like, oh, OK, they see her down the street.
And so the people at the bar let him leave,
and he went and got in his car and drove.
Wow my I don't really drink so
When we like if I go out every now and then or whatever
I almost bought one of my homegirls because she was like no no no and I fuck a snap stick
He was like no, but you were trashed you were not fucking driving and I'm not getting the car with you driving
But you got me fucked up like yeah, I don't I don't so sick that actually showed me a different part of you
So I think that's really cool that you put that PSA out. All right, same with you
Every time I say
But it's really
I don't drink what are you talking about? Oh, never mind. Oh my bad. Sorry. Yeah, we don't drink. I thought you know you don't drink as much
Every great now that I'll have a shot or something, but I don't I don't drink sleep driving is a big problem. You want to go
It's not the best thing to drive
And I don't smoke weed, I don't smoke weed when I'm drinking or driving either
These guys that drive their trucks and shit
I don't drive under intoxication at all. I don't think it's I wouldn't be a truck driver and smoke cuz I probably fall asleep
I'll be honest with you
If you notice it goes when it sometimes when I come home, I already have a blunt
It'll be rolled up and I'll sit in the car and then I'll smoke. Yeah
Before you leave the fucking parking lot you though
No, I don't I don't smoke. No, I don't because the way the way I fucking have cops arrested
They will look for any reason to fucking search my god
I think you can put me in my kitchen. Oh, no
wrong again, buddy
I was dumb back in my 20s, and I got a DUI and then I got another one for driving on my medication
Almost ten years later. So I just how long do you lose your license for?
On your second one, I haven't driven since I got my first one
So actually a place in between I try not you
Joe my uncle had a blown his fucking weave or not they hooked it up. He had a blow into his car to even start
Well, yeah, they do do that too. They'll have somebody else do it
But I know a lot of people that like, you know, I'm saying that I'll be helping or whatever and they're trying to get their license
And all that kind of shit back, you know what I mean, and they have to have those machines in their car. They can't do shit without that machine
If they're
Anything else
They can breathe into this line
You know, you know what's crazy down here? You know, you know, what's crazy down here is so unfortunately like
That fit and all shit and everything down here. It's really really bad
Oh, God, and they'll be bitches like like there's bitches that'll be you'll be sitting at a stop sign or something
And you'll just see this motherfucker like not off and just fucking be dropped like it's insane
Yeah, dude, I'm like, okay look you want to get fucked up
I don't give a shit you want to drink you and how this your life. I don't give a fuck no judgment here, right?
We're all grown. We've all done dumb shit, but do not get out in your fucking car
Where you're not an off-on shit, dude, like where you're putting everybody else's life at risk like I'm not okay with that
You're not enough that sidewalk
One step in the street you fucking just fucking sitting there like you're looking upside down kangaroo
What are you doing? It looks like a it kind of looks beautiful. It's like you're doing like some karate
Look we were coming me in front of my was coming from the south end and we were headed downtown and this guy
We're getting off the expressway and this guy's like boom boom boom on the thing and we're like I'm like what the fuck
So then I was like well, maybe he's having a medical emergency or something right well
The next thing you know he comes up and he hits one of the night night not night things but a street light things or whatever
And so I jumped out of the car, I, as you know, Marcy, I keep Narcan on me all the time because I'm having a Narcan people all the fucking time and this dude was like six foot seven and
I sit there and I caught grabbed his phone
I try to pull him out of the car and everything and as I'm doing that called his phone
I called the last number that he died which happened to be his wife
I thought he had a seizure his wife that informs me that no he he does heroin and shit like that
He might have got some bad dope. So then I go out and get my Narcan
I had the needle one that's the only one I had at the time and I stab it in his fucking leg and the crazy thing is
Sometimes when they wake up, they can get a little violent. So you have to be careful
because it was like
He's like halfway out of the car halfway in the car, but dude, it's just yeah, it's crazy like
I've been Narcan a few times so like I mean if you're just sitting there dying, you just get woke up out of your skin
You know well like when you're on a lot of medication been on a lot of summer what's do it's like literally like hitting a wall like
You hit that right when they hit you at the Narcan you wake up and you're literally ready to jump out of your skin
Like you feel like all of the withdrawals and all at once and it's
You've been not can't so
So, yeah, he yeah, he ended up being okay. Um, but yeah, there's been people that like even well Marcy I was
No, she's like the next machine they third dad
not Marcy was watching me one weekend one night when I was on outreach and I was
sitting here and I was just talking to somebody somebody was in my window and
then my team was looking and they was like Narcan and so I see you see me
take off running it took me like it took me almost a half an hour because we
lost the guy like he stopped I lost everything you had to hit him with four
time for Narcans right yeah I had him I had him with four Narcans I was doing
When the paramedics
Well
No, I hit him four times and finally I got him after doing some CPR and stuff like that
I finally got his pulse back and
Firefighters came yeah, that one was through the nose. I have a lot of those
Don't work right if they have like shit built up maybe don't go all the way up there
Um
My best friend was a
Netic and he's like because they have some like are you learn to see anything? He was like, yeah, I'm not game
Fucking
When you're doing that and set it like when you do the Narcan you can take your knuckles
as hard as you can into their chest place and you have to like push and because it hurts them but
it gives them that's what helps wake them up. That's what they tried to wake me up when they
when they killed me on the table when I got that neck injection that they broke my neck and all that
at. Yeah but Summer you know it's easier than your knuckles though there's actually one thing that's
They turn you on your side, and they go like
Boy he'll fill it
You rubbed their sternum with your knuckles. Yeah, I had a bruise right here from the nurses doing that
To try to make it seem like it was just the anesthesia I was waking up with and I clocked it in 45 seconds
I was like wait wait wait. This is motherfucking Narcan. Why'd you guys have to Narcan me?
They weren't supposed to give me any opiates
Did they lift your feet up at all?
And Nargant only works with Obians just so you all know, okay?
Yeah, a lot of usually they're like now having died or knocked out they'll lift your feet up
And they rub your chest like that
So I get you to wake back up when you're like if you ever get like submitted out
They'll lift your feet up and rub your chest like that. I've never seen the lift your feet up thing
I've never heard that either, but yeah, that's a thing. I guess I mean
Lift your feet up. Why do they lift their feet up? I don't know. Maybe blood flow. I don't I don't understand it
Maybe blood flow. I don't even understand that at all, but they do lift their feet up
I don't know why I responded to a shitload of overdoses and we've never looked at their feet
Oh, no, no, no, you have C fighters when they get knocked out like fighters when they get knocked out
They lift their feet up and they love their chest. What they do for a shock
Or shock. Okay. I think that's procedure for shock
Yeah, I think it will know if you well. Yeah, that doesn't make sense though. None of them think about it
Yeah
What Marcy showed everybody should have some of that in their car or in their backpacks or purses or anything like
You can get it health departments health departments usually give it away for free
Now in a lot of areas they'll they have like the dispensers
Yep, but if you go to your local health departments, they will give it to you for free don't buy it
Yeah, and some hospitals have like the you know, like the stance of machines that used to have the chips and stuff in it
They'll have those dark hand ones like that and those are free as well
Summer what would happen if you rip one without what would happen if you just rip one would it do anything to you?
No, it's just it. It's just okay. No, it's an epidural pins. You get it's like a fucking adrenaline shot
No
You're not gonna get half of it. It's not you're not gonna overdose on it
I think the problem with Naxalone or whatever those suboxone is that people think that it's a methadone, right exactly the same thing methadone is that people don't know the science of it, it's actually an opiate, but I believe it's mixed with, I don't know if it's mixed with or if it's a different kind of opiate.
cute um like kind of a painkiller it's not like a strong painkiller it's not like anything like
that i think it just like for as far with the suboxone is it kind of helps with keeping the
the withdrawal symptoms away like pink you know painkillers i think it was like a lot thinner though
But it has naloxaline in it and the naloxaline, if you have any opiate in your system, it will...
Dude, I stepped out the other day, oh, I shouldn't say that, okay.
A couple months ago, he cut his finger and I had to take him to the hospital, he's bleeding out so much, he takes blood thinners.
He also takes pain pills.
I'm like, he's fucking bleeding out so much, I had to take him to the fucking hospital, I couldn't get him to stop.
I think that has more to do with the blood thinners than the pain pills.
Did you raise his hand above it?
I said, hey, listen, sir, the burden of proof is on you
That's what I said
Yeah, I've been going to pain management and have
Are you ever gonna take that?
11 damn
Yeah, whenever whenever it range on pain
Yeah
I'm in pain every day all the time every time when I wake up. Yeah, but I'm on methadone
I take methadone now, which helps with the pain. It actually does help with the pain
So and it's a long lasting one
So I only have to take it once or do a split dose, you know, half in the morning half at night
So, yeah
Depending on how well like I can get a surgeon that did my neck to do my lower back to do the revision surgery
Or the broken screw back and he does as good of a job. I'm gonna that tomorrow
And I know I can definitely
That'd be great. Go pink. That would be amazing
No, I'm keeping it brown
You know who had really bad back pain years ago this guy guy Jerry Lewis
Old comedian. He had very bad back pain and all of a sudden he told the story about the doctor put some kind of electrical device in his back
And he said it was all gone. He had no fucking pain after that. That's a pain stimulator
A battery pack in your hip you get a remote for it and then they run the lines up
into wherever your pain area is, and it basically sends
electric, that's like an eternal three years ago.
Yeah, I had back then, I took off the CBD gummies.
Okay, depending on where your pain is, what your pain is,
those like, we looked into it for me when my lower back
first went out.
And you have to go through a whole psychological clearance and all that shit.
See a psych doctor for a little bit and do all the testing and all that, and you get a paid for it.
And then when the doctor actually got like all of the testing and everything done
He said that there was that the way that the anatomy was with my lower back
It wouldn't work for for the thing that I had because my my nerve roots were crushed in my lower back
So after they're crushed and not just being pinched and then you kind of
What was crush yet this yet this
No, the nerve root. Well, the disc had done bilateral perfusions, so they went out on both sides.
so it wasn't like one side or the other or front and back it was just like everywhere pretty much
L5S1 so the very bottom right above my tailbone um and so I got a fusion and when I got the fusion
done we had only talked about doing one level but the doctor said if we had discussed doing both
levels the L4L5 as well that he would have done that one too because that was a huge problem so
Um kind of destabilize everything to make it to that one screw just didn't
Didn't heal right and it broke, you know
Yeah, but so we we'd help you
We'd help me just wait helps me my mind. Yeah, like definitely
It distracts you. Yeah, and then definitely like if you get the right kind of cdb or thc, um, it can decrease pain. Yeah
Yeah, so it takes attention away
Mm-hmm. Everyone's brains different. That's why they have so many different kinds of drugs for the same kind of almost
I got the good shit
And all that, you know, like it depends on how how well it works with your brain and dip chemistry
That's why I don't care. Okay. Who you work for some people
Like it ends work for some people. They don't for others
If you get the wrong pain it could cripple you. Yeah, it doesn't matter who you are. It could be yep
Most in shape person best athlete of the world, but yeah, that pain will fuck you up. Yeah
Yeah, Marcy. Let me tell you guys Marcy looks like
Little out before she had her surgery and shit like Marcy was fucked up dude
Like it was it was sad to watch her in so much pain all the time
Oh, it's hard. She's had her surgery, baby. You have bounced back like holler. You look so gorgeous
I'm feeling good. I'm trying to get my movement back
I can put my hands up now.
She was still amazing, but you can tell she was always in pain.
I was always in pain.
Yeah, my neck was like, my head was on my shoulder.
I had it dislocated.
That's how she was like that.
Do that again, Mars.
She was like that literally all the time.
Yeah
Me to look at those old streams because I see that and I know how much pain I was in even though I'm cracking jokes and still being like myself
You know, I was doing that girl. I was doing the fucking badass
Amazing what the neck you tell me what that neck? Yeah, girl. Ha ha ha
Yeah, her neck be doing a lot, baby
Mm-hmm
It was like put that bitch to work
But she did I mean like she really
Has that in common though
Because she used to be in pain a lot all the time like it was it was sad
But she had that surgery and I mean she's done her there, you know work through it or whatever
But she's it's done a hundred percent on her
Good
Well, so what's up fuckers?
Hmm
And I'm just reading some of the chat
Everyone's having fun. It looks like hi loser. Hey, just I'm still waiting for psyche to respond to my dick pic
I guess that's funky but Justin dinner tonight. He hasn't respond in
He broke up with her. I'm starting to feel self-conscious. At least you wait till after dinner, Bob Boyle
I don't think it was our fault. I think it was just he's in the bed. No, we didn't do anything
I think I think they'll make up. I think they'll make up. Hey loser. Hey loser. Hey Memphis. I'm smoking meth right now
What was that what was that you will boil
I don't know when the fuck. I'm so conscious because psyche isn't responding to my dick pics
You didn't send me at your dick pic. I saw it's a picture of a woman walking man
Let's go babe
Summer so he has my offer ever offered to pay you anything
No, have I ever asked you?
No
So I could ever offer to pay you anything. Yes
Well, you did send me the clip and you did if you had a clip you pay me. Yes
I I said I told you the other night goes and I said I said I'm not gonna open the panel and I said unless you promise that you're
Gonna you're gonna sponsor it and you said you promised and you said just open the panel I'll sponsor
I'll send us you I said promise like no, I think it looks I have no mind peanut
But now if I had I'd never once ever
How many times I've been joining for like over and well over you I never fucking
I never heard that, I didn't record it today.
But you know what, there's nothing wrong with supporting the people that give you a place
to hang out and have a good time and all that.
Ain't nothing wrong with that, that's not what I'm talking about at all.
Okay, then what's your point?
Okay, so you donated tonight, good job.
I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like I
I think if there's a there's a demand then it's like and it's like at least if like people someone's sponsors the panel Bill
Kick they'll probably keep the person in line to keep it on topic or keep it interesting or not to be whatever and then it's like
It's also
Call it. I think they call it like an executive producer, right?
I like the executive producer credit. You kind of like not if you want to if you want to have that
You have to pay to be here. That's pay to play that. Yeah, I mean, you don't have to
One person one person pays and it one person pays and I could I get them an appetite like an MLM sponsor
I'm not going to the first the first streamer at MLM. I'm not making an MLM
By the way, none of you fuckers underneath me. I think I'm not none of you fuckers underneath me. I don't care if anyone
We're not wet
None of them they say like oh
What are we talking about?
You're not getting your money back. Is that what you want? We're not complaining. I'm saying I don't understand
It's really
goes
Make a big bold
You're paying to play so what's the big deal? Yeah, no refunds
So we have to pay to play from now on if I was ever like a Chinese
Discount store if I know if I was to like as simple as that I got your back psyche
Should okay, can we can we let Alex back on or what did you do what I could do?
Did he pay to play? I don't know did he pay no he has he hasn't paid no no, but it's a
One person pays for the end and everyone could go on the panel for it's like for a few hours
They sponsor the panel and then and if everybody can go in the open
They start acting like a dick kick them off again, okay?
He's actually gonna pay first you
Can you take the banner down
That's crazy
Give me money Alex. Give me money
Why you gotta act like a dick for
Let him join dude
He's insulting me and he's like
Okay, you paid yesterday to play
Yeah, that was I'm sure that was well after 12. Thank you. Hey ghost ghost if you have an advertisement
I'll put it on my my community board, okay?
Yeah, it's called the hot girl summer
Okay
I'll donate your band time to summer okay. Yeah done done
Oh, I'll have the banner up during my my next solo and we are going natural
Alex join
You don't want to listen to Alex cry for four fucking hours about you don't have to you guys
You have the freedom to kick him whenever you want
That's what he does, motherfuckers
He fucking repeats the same shit for hours
You don't want to get invested in that
I know you're into that shit, I know you like that
fucking autistic shit, ghost
Autistic shit
What do you mean autistic?
It's like fucking him
You repeat the same shit over and over again
What do you mean by that?
Oh, you kind of heard me saying you heard
Well, would you like me not to say you lost the debate?
Would you like me not to say that, sir?
Did I offend you?
Did I offend you by saying you're hurt?
Did I offend you by that?
Sir, you lost the debate, sir.
There was no debate.
Did I offend you by saying you're hurt?
Because, sir, I respect you as a gentleman myself.
And I say you hurt again around you in person.
You hurt?
See, I can do that shit, too.
Would you like me not to say that?
I could do it for fucking hours, too, asshole.
I don't know.
Would you like me not to say that?
Don't fuck.
That's what I'm asking, say yes or no.
Are making an hour long debate
If you don't like me to say that I won't say it. What are you talking about?
Do you want me to say you heard or not? Is that what i'm talking about? What are you talking about?
Actually, I don't give a fuck I do with the fuck of what you heard shut the fuck up
Lost what
The fuck up I paid the cheese that you heard
I'll put that on for them. So what you arguing about? He's here. All right, nothing
Yeah, but let my main house talk let him crash out real quick. You're fucking too retarded do it. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you
Thank you. Finally. Thank you
Thank you for putting on a podium. Let him talk. Let him talk. Oh, thanks losers
I run this shit you little cockerel to go below me
I am the king so you're talking because I allow it
But it's okay. I'm on board with you
I'm on board. I need a number one in number two number three
The point is that summer should be vanished
Yeah, that's true, but why I should that last one is not forty four
That is the foot over 90 year-old
Forties and I'll have one yourself this space looks a wrinkle her forehead looks like she's 90 that's scary
And then tattoos aren't doing no good. You're older than I am Alex. So go fucking suck a dick tattoos are fine
It's like king glee night is first the Persian and ghost you better shut the fuck up
We don't have another way to hang out at so you can suck a dick too, but what would you say?
Well, I'll play games sue motherfucker. So you better stop by make you crash out. You fucking care bear a little bitch
Well, ma'am, I'd rather be a care bear looking bitch than a bitch that needs to be a care of, you heard?
Why don't you shake your tits a little bit more?
Bitch, I'm a wife. I'm supposed to be taken care of, you dumb fuck.
You're a wife. You're a wife. You shouldn't be shaking your tits, dumb dumb.
I didn't see them now.
Yeah, I can show my boobs. I can show my fucking cleavage.
Yeah, yeah, right there, right there.
Yeah, your husband likes that, too.
Babies!
Yeah
Where's your husband
He doesn't need to show me show now you're ready you ready for this
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
He's over there. He's a fucking son. Let me talk to your husband.
I'm pretty much this look like how he would sound.
May I talk to your husband?
You can suck a dick is what you can do.
Fuck you, I'll talk to my husband before, bitch.
I ain't gonna suck nothing. I wanna talk to your husband.
I'll talk to your fucking wife.
Oh, that's right. You ain't got one, bitch.
Don't feel like a ghost. You look like a fat ghost.
I would, if I had a wife like you, trust me.
You ain't got one, though, so you fat fuck.
Yeah, can I talk to your husband?
You ain't got one, you fat fuck.
Chicken or titties whore
Do stupid after the conversation you're too much of a slut
So, uh, send to tell you what to do
Please keep it coming because i'm gonna slow remember this
I want him to hear it
Now keep going talk. No, I want him to hear it though. It's important. Fuck bitch
It's important for watch you shake your titties I'll do get the rocks
I'll do a get the rocks why don't you shake your titties a little bit
Nobody wants to see that
Doing it like synchronized
Enjoy that motherfucker. That's crazy. You too bitch. How about this? How about this in your fucking ass?
Play with me
He's like this fuck
Vinnie, are you the real Vinnie? Is it Vinnie Pots and Pans? Is it? Hold on Vinnie?
Vinnie, no, hold on. I said one name. I don't want to put you to sleep. It's real name.
Just remember how much you're filling yourself tonight, ghost.
Remember that bitch.
Who's this I keep the same energy bitch. Oh, no you won't cuz you're always kissing somebody's ass, but I got you I promise you
Did you just shake your tits at men on the internet?
Word. I can shake my tits wherever the fuck I want through my titties
They're mine as well. You're not my husband. So now where he's on the menu, you may or may not accept him
I mean I'm
Secure man
I'm gonna burn you the fuck up. You know, I am go ahead
You're just you're just burning a bridge is all you've done tonight. Go ahead
Go with your argument because I'm gonna burn that ass
You're disgusting
How am I just asking I
Don't want my woman dancing on in the man flash
Disgusting
No, and yeah, exactly
Another man
Were you not just showing, were you not just like bouncing the titties?
Marcy, were you not?
Not for you, bitch!
Finally in the room
You think my husband's gonna waste I'm talking to some lowly fat bastard
His wife you sit in there playing the game
Mine doesn't either done fuck
Well, I'm not a don't fuck cuz I like really good games
You are though. He's done fuck cuz you are let's other men play with his girls kiddies
I'm on YouTube are you not I'm the only one touching them
You're stupid as fuck dude. You're dumb and you're lame
About the next bands bitch
What a fucking fact
I
Go ahead and explain yourself. So I'm about to burn it up. I want to talk to you
Who's this guy right here this guy they say vinyl are you there to say yes or no? I want both of them I know I
Can't hear you. You're not saying anything
Okay, I'm just gonna take you off. I can't hear you. You're on the microphone son. Okay, there is a thing
Oh, yeah
Summer something
Our husbands are around you idiot. I don't know what you're talking about. I know you retard. That's my argument
Imagine for simp in the next
Worrying about getting mad over the next bit
They're they're fucking simps yard. You have no you had you don't have a
You don't have the right to even think about talking about the next man's relationship
I should never marry a woman like you. You have nobody. You have nobody. So it doesn't matter
I'd rather nobody than a fucking saint. Yeah, especially a whore. Good
Nobody has nips
Every woman is allowed to do whatever
What are we trying to shame them? What are you doing?
True
We haven't done anything fucking wrong
It was sexual in nature
Oh, he's asexual that's what it is. That's what it is. Yeah
All right, I'm gonna have to hit you with it and I didn't want to do some dude tits in your face
Okay, the burden of proof on you how am I asexual go ahead and say show me your tits because you don't like tits
Oh, maybe like I do I love tits. I love my girl
Who does that I just want to see your horse that's on the line even psyche was having a good time looking at tits
Well, what's wrong with you? You're a fucking idiot
You're weird, bro. Yeah. Yeah. How am I go ahead and explain you make the argument go ahead
Fuck it, I'll take all four of you. Let's run that bitch dog
One in the chat if you like to shake it on the screen. You're talking to Sam. She fucking retard
They want
that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that
How am I mad? Go ahead and explain. Let me sit back. You'll hear you. Run it back. All you want. How am I mad?
I get you. I win. How am I mad? Go ahead.
How am I mad?
Piss them off. Piss them off. Go ahead.
How am I?
Who's the Muslim
Go fuck yourself dude
Yeah
I don't want my woman
So what's your fucking problem, I don't like me personally I don't like tits
You are nobody
And I can tell you would that be an argument for it. There's no action. You gay. He said he's gay. He said he's gay
Well, that's what it has to be
About somebody yet what the next person's doing your lame is
Why don't you guys go somewhere together?
I'm not mad. I'm doing get the rocks
To free coffee
Sorry keep it up ghost you ain't doing nothing but hurt yourself. I promise you that
We don't give a fuck
Cuz you're lame
Okay, what am I doing? You're taking fun in and joking around to the next level and being a fucking prick
So it's cool. You do you I promise you it's gonna bite you now. Do you think it's fun to your husband?
You shake your tits, bitch. You're not my husband
You know what my husband says
her husband is probably
you know what his hands and face was
in between the panel
hony mary a fucking son
i'd rather talk to him
in between the panel
and that ellipsoid
what do i look like letting some drunk nobody
talk to my fucking husband
You ain't my god damn daddy
Your lame is fuck bitch
I don't talk to a whore
I
Was a mind of a simp like I'm interested you're a mind of a bitch be rude my husband don't talk to bitches dude
I haven't fucked around with anybody else, he talks about horses, he just fucked them.
It's December 14, 2007, so.
Gotcha, ghosts. I promise you that.
He's a child.
I've done tonight.
What do you promise me?
That sounds like a threat.
You're a bitch.
I got you, didn't I?
We'll see.
Now you didn't.
No, you didn't.
All you did was burn a fucking bridge, and that's all you did, bitch.
Oh, I said
You're mad about what the next man's bitch is doing you're stupid fuck
Dude my husband is right here. It's what the fuck are you talking about?
You like some used goods you sure it's on you you like some use guys. Let me talk to that man
Only fans you dumb fuck you think my husband doesn't know that
May I talk to the man to see how he actually feels? Let me talk to him
It's not even a fucking business what our relationship is. Why are you trying to talk to him?
Why is there a way to bed? Let me talk to him.
He said he doesn't have anything to say to you.
Fuck a dick!
So they're gonna run? They're gonna let them bitches be whores?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Let me talk to them. Let me see how they actually feel about it.
How is doing this of being a whore?
Says the dude that has nobody minding.
Oh my god, you get checked.
You're not gonna answer it. Let me talk to them. Yeah, they actually told us the guy
You know what they're gonna say, what are you gonna say?
You guys are scared of that because you know what would happen
Do you think our husbands don't know what we're wearing do you not think they haven't been around us all day?
I would like to talk to him and see how he feels about you wearing that but you
You're not putting money in any of our pockets. Why do you think we give a fuck what you're talking about?
You're not my mommy. You're my dad. Are you stupid? I?
Won that one though. Yeah nothing bitch
You wouldn't let me talk
Of the year award he doesn't let you because yeah, not that attractive. He's doing what do you because you want to hit
That's the only reason he's there
Straight up down
But I'm going back
Now he's my best friend. We have fun and laugh together. So that's why I fucking won this one
I don't stick around for fucking almost 20 years with somebody. I'm here. I'm not gonna wait eight hours
I went no say it again. Say it again. You won this one say it again. I won this one brother say it again
Did you win this room say it again
All I know is that he delivered the Red Bull so must have done my job
Now fuck it. I'll say to get my one this one fucking rain man
If Chris is awake, he understands that. I don't know if he's awake.
I got my Red Bull delivery today, bitch.
Another fucking New Yorker.
Fucking stupid.
Hey, boy, what happened to you being funky?
I'll give you 30 seconds.
I heard me wrong.
Suck a dick after them 30 seconds. What you're not
So you're not gonna do either way
My husband went to bed, I'm not gonna wake him up
You're fucking lame, dude
Are you stupid dude? He said he didn't want to talk to you as well. He was like what somebody that doesn't like titties
No, I don't want to talk to them
He'd be like are you fucking like what's wrong with you like dick or something dude? Oh
Dear
You don't care if I shake them that's okay
You could shake the police. Can you please stop doing that? It's offensive to me. Please. Don't do that
Please stop. It's very burning my eyes
The retina
Okay, good. All right, I'm glad you're good. There you go. See when you get laid sometimes you can make up
You just had the agreement for the makeup sex didn't you Justin?
Officer Boyle, is it officer or deputy?
Huh?
Midway heaven.
You stop midway?
Midway.
They were fucking and she said, oh god, and then he got fucking mad, that's what happened.
That's what pissed you off, right?
Oh shit.
Oh god.
Would you call me
Stopped midway
You got to get used to it
Get on some falling spray. Oh my god flashbacks flashbacks
Poor ghost man, he's like terminally in cell
Idiot dude. I like to speak easy his lady's not giving him any over there, too
Is that really his pick you showed?
Ghost pick?
Yeah, he shows face on Psyche's panel.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, look at that face, dude.
That screams himself.
That dude's bad at looking at titties.
Holy shit.
You heard?
Yeah, Lily.
Fuckin idiot. He looks like he's seen a ghost
Hey, you see no titties in a long time, it's like it's mad
He's mad each one of our
Don't ask me man, I don't know I
Don't know my husband told me if I wanted to sell pictures of my tits. He would have no problem with that
We wouldn't be a single income household that way, but I'm not gonna do that
That's the guy that's bitchin about titties you guys, right that's it
So
Summer you tried you try to get me out. I mean you really did try to get all mixed in he said dude
He's so dumb like I'm just over him
Yeah, oh the fucking skunks are out there again faster a guy
Can't scare these bitches away either go go spray them. I hit him with the oh
Shit, okay, I
Guess I'm for breeze. I've heard it, but it didn't spray. I
Don't know if that one can fit underneath the thing. I heard they do a dance
They do like a quick dance and then they fucking scream
He looked like he looked like he was like all right stop and he turned around and looked at the door
And he like took this like wide-legged stance and looked at me, and I was like oh fuck
And then he turned around and put him around so now I get to go and get the food that's out here
At least or so
Yeah
Yeah, boy, I think you fucked up
You gotta fix this
She's a good girl
She's got money I like
What more do you want really a dope woman and she's beautiful
Yeah, exactly. What do you what more do you need and she cares about Justin you can tell?
Yep, and
She has money. Don't forget that
When you're ready
Right midnight
I was like everybody in the chat hit one except for go
Even the people that were muslims, dude
I had props to the muslim brothers and sisters out there
I'm not a muslim, but we're all brothers and sisters
Shout out to all the muslims out there
Hello!
Shout out to all the muslims that aren't joining
9-1-1 again
Shout out to you
Cheers to them
Were you alive when that happened I was there
Cheers
You know what? He was in the fifth plane. He was still alive. You guys know about the fifth plane, right? Yeah
That's weird, right? It just fucking disappeared. They never said anything
I don't know. I don't know.
So I'm gonna turn to a demon but I don't know if he's backstage
Yeah, but who is it? Is that who's saying is that's the one he had up early?
Yeah, he's fucked up a second ago, but nobody
They didn't say shit. Oh, no, don't do it. Yeah, the microphone wasn't working. I'm gonna turn into a team. No, man
Don't do it man. I need another shot right now
He's fucking doing it
I'm going to get kicked out of Scythe's right now.
I'm going to get kicked out.
I can see it now. It's coming.
That's what he said.
Oh yeah.
The boys cry.
I thought that bitch has got hit by a car last night
It's okay, they can't really like scare them scaring away, you know, like all right the other day
Scare what away?
Yeah, you can't you don't want to get sprayed
You smell it sometimes you're striving by
Smells really strong.
The thing like turned around and looked at the door and it looked like it was about to do like a fucking like flash dance or some shit.
Uh-huh.
That was a lot.
I'll be quiet.
I'm not gonna open the door yet though.
You've never been skunked.
Have you guys ever been skunked?
No.
Vinyl says his mic works.
Vinyl, right in the back so we can see you.
Is that you, wait is that, is that Vinyl?
Patrick
I know is that you that's me
What up? Can you hear me? Yeah, I can hear you. All right. How you doing?
Did you come to weigh in on the city fucking discussion I remember this guy. He came here to look at the days
I said the city fucking
Boobies are showing this is Canada drives brother
Can you speak for a second so you hear you what's up, man? I'm shy
What's up, Seb? You were right down the back. Do you have anything to say?
Yeah, I got a doctor Patrick. Patrick, I'll give you ten bucks to take that faggot Gotti off the panel.
Why would I do?
And to take his wrench away, I'll give you 25 bucks.
Oh, Seb, can you afford 25, Seb?
I'll give him a cashier's check, Gotti. You faggot.
A cashier's check. Oh, how nice.
Who's that?
He's got a bounce like you.
All the check is in saying anything
Tell me one thing why do you go to bathhouses with other men and swim with other men are you gay God?
Everyone knows that you're gay now stop abusing of your wrench
Go ahead tell us your problem with gay Sebastian
That's it. I'll give you 25 bucks. If they got his wrench away. What do you think of that?
It was the land of freedom all I hear is these American motherfucking men being stupid little fucking people wanting to control everybody
Oh, really?
Life literally goes on everyone's panel when they desperate for it.
Every individual.
And abuses of the wrench, doesn't he?
Who cares?
Why are you here?
You're always on the panel, man.
You're always talking about me.
Why do you tie me out when I said that you went to Bath House?
Are you mad about that?
No, maybe you're mad man. Maybe you're jealous of me. That's why you tied me out for a reason, didn't you?
I'm not yelling, you're yelling.
Is that houses even a good thing you want?
I'm gonna give a cash register to Patrick to take your wrench away. What do you think of that?
You live in a shithole. You're talking about me?
He got in a fucking time machine and came back from 1825, what the fuck?
I haven't heard about a bathhouse in here.
Are you afraid that your wrench will be taken away once I give Patrick a cashier's check?
Nobody gives a fuck about a wrench, Brad.
Why don't you get a discount?
No, Marcy, you don't understand it. God he abuses of the ranch times people out for fun for no reason
I just told you because he time me out for no reason twice
He knows I'm funnier than him
No, no, not him. No, that was somebody else. You got a lot of haters out there
Yeah, listen to me, he's jealous of that gaudy guy is jealous of me because I don't give him 40% off liposuction surgery
He's very jealous of me. I mean, he's a very upset with that
Why you'd get 40% off like 40% up to my earlier customer
I'm not gonna get him 40% off his liposuction
Do you do surgery say I?
Don't do surgery the surgeons take care of that me
I do the marketing and the operations and development strategy and operation. Can we get you to get that guy go?
That's not a good breast augmentation. So you want to be mad at us when we show our he needs liposuction surgery that goes guy
Well, he needs some titties so he don't get mad when we show ours
I don't think the surgeon do that. He only specialized in liposuction surgery. It's a liposuction surgery clinic. Oh
So does he do VBLs or no? Actually, he could probably use some of that, too
No, and maybe maybe he's overweight. Maybe he wants to take a bit of a bit of fat off his body
I can I can help him with that
Like a like conniated
One person not getting the discount. That's gaudy. That's for
You know why I'm not giving you the discount because you time me up for no reason you punk why why you mad
You're mad because you're Joe's man you time me out to take out your frustrations. Are you all right?
Are you going to keep crying about him timing you out or are you going to fuck him?
Oh, who's crying? Maybe he's crying. I'm not crying.
That's okay. That's me there and slick on my phone though. There we go. Here we go. This is for you step
Yeah, I got he stopped crying
I'm crying in the bathhouses with other men swimming in the pools with other men
Marcy do you know who this guy is I've known for years this guy goes on every panel China
This guy's jealous me he's been jealous me for a long time Marcy obviously don't know I've known for years this guy's a punk
Yeah, that's for sure. Yeah, why are you so upset because you got timed out once? Guess what? I've been timed out before.
Actually, were you there? Psyche you there?
Psyche you there?
We're at one crop, baby, and another crop, baby.
Psyche, I'll give you the cash. Just check that they guys rent away.
You think it's gonna work? You think it's gonna work?
25 bucks.
I don't think I ever think he's shaking
Just trying to find out who are these
That's too much. I'll give him 25 bucks savings your bum. Just like a 25
I'll give it to him to take his wrench away and off the panel
I'll make it $200 to take a wrench away. Well, I don't know. That's too much. Come on
Negotiation on that too expensive, you know me kens. I gotta collect you get $200. Come on now
I can't afford that shit. You can't get his wrench stick in the way if you're not gonna pay to play
Nothing just chillin man. How you been?
How much you weigh now about to 60 to 50 you brought some weight, didn't you?
Yeah, I stress eating man. You've been stressing me out. Follow me to every panel
I'm not gonna be able to give it a 40% off. Got it. I can't help you
You're on your own son a little nip talk, I'll be all set
That guy is obese
Oh, he's obese. All right. Oh, be some little he's overweights
He's a bed wetter
Some women think that's a turn on it can be some being a boy
I
Was a big bra man in a personal relationship though
Oh, there's nothing funny about the fact that you're in con and gaudy
It's no laughing matter come on man, this isn't a sign for what is your name black cat
You can't do all the sidecoats here. I'm not doing any sidecoats right now, Goddy. This is my material
Do I hear you? Yeah, it's me, but it's not funny. This isn't Vandalay industry. It's my dreams. Nothing's gonna stop me now, Goddy
Your material sucks though dude. Why are you talking?
You've never watched that sitcom Perfect Strangers? Yeah, I love that. Remember that the intro
Yeah, it's my life. It's my dreams. Nothing's gonna stop me now the place in Chicago life will suction surgery my friend lame
How old are you dude?
Yeah, he's older you
I'm guessing
I mean, you're like
Who's that who's talking right now?
God you summers is that you summer miss?
now, I
Don't know summer answer your question. I'm 44
He looks like you're like you're like 10
No, I got he's acting like that got a times people out for no reason simply because I refused to give him 40% off his label
So okay, how many times how many times he's on you out?
I don't have many times
I'm not defending him. I'm just finding you annoying
right
For hours now talking nonsense. I don't get you guys. I don't get you junkies and prostitutes
You've been on the panel for hours talking. I got it comes on sober on the panel you guys give them a
Maybe out of sober
I don't even drink. I don't fucking
What's wrong team team are you in here in the clinic? We asked them to sober up at least 48 hours prior to surgery
Huh?
What the fuck are you talking about people to come in for surgery?
We don't care. We gotta clean up. We don't care. 48 hours before surgery. That's the protocol.
That's what you have in the fucking surgery dude. No one cares. You don't do the surgery.
What are you talking about? You're a sales rep. Shut the fuck up.
Well, of course on the silver. I'm just I was telling you how it goes
You have nothing to do with the surgery you do some fucking paper
They actually tell people to sober up
I take care of the marketing aspect
No, maybe it's true what they say maybe you are a prostitute, maybe you are a dumb prostitute. Maybe it's true what they say about you
Maybe they were right
Maybe the people that were saying that were right about you
First we lose ghost then we get Sebastian. So after Sebastian
Who's that ghost guy is starting to make sense when I think about Alex who who's gonna come after?
You me what do you have to say you me God either more I think about it the more I love chicken a great great meat
about what I
Don't like I don't like him
He blocked me in like two years. Who's Sebastian? Oh, yeah, I don't know
You're
You're talking one time and you guys talking one time. I can't understand you with you. It's talking. We don't want to talk at one time
Yeah, 40% off in this conversation doesn't happen
Discount is not available for everyone. It's a limited time offer only for certain clients certain valued clients
Mm-hmm
Okay
How fat are you? Are you out? What's your current weight and measurements? I weigh 125 and I'm five foot seven
500 pounds on come on. How you being silly about 350
Well
Definitely you could use liposuction search
Yeah, I'm about 350 pounds
Yeah, you're putting me to sleep though
Think of the reds they won four games straight right now
Fuck the reds
Well, who's your team? What do you like?
The white socks are done, they're not even making the playoff
Two years in a row in the American League there white socks need an owner
that they need everything
Ohio is is in second running to be the next Florida man
Southern Ohio. That's a good state. That's a good part of the next
Florida man. Yeah, the whole state. That's all for everybody. Yep. Speaking of bath salts, Vyna, what's wrong with you?
Speaking of bath salts, Gotti, what were you doing that?
In that bathtub
That I would I never thought I would see the tigers at the top. I grew up in
Change
Do that again Marcy
His mic up. He's really low
That's hot. Who's this fat baby?
That's me. I was showing a picture. So you see where I need liposuction at
I'm sexy
There we go, that's where that's me earlier
I want the fat removing your belly. Do you do you? Yeah
I can be arranged
All right, cool
Does she get 40% off or is that we'll see we'll see about that
I'll need to think about it. You're a shitty marketer, bro. Just kidding. Yeah, you're a horrible marketer
an excellent marketer
I might take back that somewhere else. Yep. Oh, that's your business. That's your right. That's your decision. It's your choice. Oh
Now people are allowed
I might be in a problem Scott now. It's up to her discretion
I thought we were talking about how a body couldn't go to fucking
Backhouses and shit like it was not a lot or like the other companies aren't gonna offer you 40% off. I offer that
God he goes wherever he wants
God he goes to bathhouses with men. He's obviously gay
You know how he knows that
He's I heard it through the grapevine. He's like everything through one exhale. Like it's how you talk
Honey, I've heard it through the grapevine that you've been hanging around the bath houses with other men in a swimming pool
You're right. You've been watching me
Some hot jacuzzi I've been getting the reports
I've been reading the transcripts
Because you're not into my style
Not much in your style either summer whatever your name is. What style is it? What style is it? Well, don't judge me
Don't just ask
I'm gonna go so
It's where right
These lip-dart women these lip-dart prostitutes why are they so agitated
How do they see magitated tonight? Maybe give them a tranquilizer that help them
Yeah
Minister adults of 200 grams of tranquilizer
Maybe you son to get them off stage. I do very well actually
Yes, I can see that something else I do better than you. So again, what's your point? There's one person that does better than you got it
You see how these people I'm just getting
Seriously
I was watching your videos the other day my summer there hot summer mess
Oh, it's a big fat black guy in the truck
What's wrong with him being black and the SUV? Who's that fat guy guy?
Say your bimber is at your boyfriend, who's that person who's that character?
Pressing him because he's fat and he needs liposuction surgery
I'll take a tummy tuck. How are you tonight? I don't need a liposuction
Yeah, you need the liposuction surgery. See look at you. Are you blind?
You're obviously more than a little beast a tummy tuck my guy
I've seen you on camera. Are you down?
So you're the fattest thing I've ever seen and I've been on so far
Me tuck I'm down. You're the fattest thing. I've ever seen sick
You just gotta give me a couple months to lose the way I lose it
are you going to lose it on a kettle dive?
well I know how to do it
I've lost like 120 pounds a few times
oh yeah?
yeah
how much did you weigh before?
my top weight was like 330
And you lost 120 pounds you my lot my minimum my lowest weight my lowest weight was like
160 170 that's outstanding
Maybe like 150 I forgot what kind of aids that's you the old lady's incredible weight loss
that's not you
Hold on is that you me is that you when you were a baby? I could lose a hundred pounds in a few months and her okay
No, no, she says she's the lady based on what role I'm
Think a look at the jet here
Using the glasses is the body. Yeah, you have the glasses. That's why it's not because I I I don't wearing it
No, don't look like you that looks like an old lady
that's me
I swear to god mr. Gotti
well here's the thing
here's the thing
you're judging where somebody else looks like
summer
the private eyes are watching
but nobody can see what you look like
work on your material
they watch your every move
the private eyes
the problem
with Gotti with you judging
what somebody else looks like
Is that you're not showing what you look like yourself?
You're saying that this person looks like this, but you're not even showing
Buddy oh you need to lose it again
Yeah, yeah, well you've done it before you can do it again. Yeah, what's up when he goes back? Yeah, dude
I got cast in a row. I'm like why
Without having surgery to that's beautiful. I was cast I was cast in a I was cast everyone
Basically
Let me type in
Mr. Psyche what do you have for dinner time?
I can't have to come up and say hi.
You did so well that I'd like to give you the award
for Outstanding Achievement in the field of excellence.
Ga ga ga.
Outstanding Achievement in the field of excellence.
Yes.
Ga ga ga.
Outstanding Achievement in the field of excellence.
I'm into that.
I would love to have that on my mantle.
Yeah, I had it weird.
What was that?
What is that?
You don't know Goo Goo Ga Ga?
Google Gaga
Psyche please my song. I'm not coming back open the stupid channel
Okay, no more Caloos on the side chat there another Joe's Buck. I see
Some psyche don't play the song
I mean, I've played it already. I mean, he was talking over it
It's it kind of sucks
Yeah, it pops up
the
Oh, that's a cute kitty.
Is that a real kitty?
Yes, but she's been on my lap the whole time.
What is your name?
What's her name?
Alexander McQueen.
What is your cat name?
Who's the video by Marcy?
Her name is Kate.
I don't know. I don't know.
I just typed it out. It's like
it's like a million videos.
Yeah. At the end. Sorry. And
it's like it looks like a picture
from TPP. It's a screen grab.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm trying to play once so we never have to hear it again.
What the fuck?
What is it? Somebody made that?
Somebody made that like randomly after being on TVB with Alex and like Alex just loves it.
He was so excited.
He felt like a celebrity.
That was awesome.
He was like mine, but he likes that one.
He likes that one, but he doesn't mind.
I mean, it was heartfelt.
Alex, you should be ashamed, dude.
He's demanding it.
Honestly.
That's the play of your stupid song now.
There you go.
Now are you happy, Alex?
Okay, Alex.
You can do it.
Happy.
You fucking made that.
Yeah, it's not really his name.
It was just bad.
It was bad.
It was bad, Alex.
Wow.
It was bad.
You're like, dude, he's a ghost, bro.
You're garbage, man.
The fucking base was all the way up, too.
Wow.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
That's not his channel. No, it's the Roast Channel. Okay. Okay, Marcy Fox and Easy Cameras is involved. Oh, that is Kat Vaga, aka Karisma Hernandez, aka the evil, I am the evil one, aka Devil or Satan, aka...
Jesus, what the fuck?
Yeah, it's a little obsessive, just a little bit.
Hold on, she's Karisma?
Yeah, yeah, we'll never play that again. That's the last time you'll hear that song.
I'm I guarantee you won't be the last time you hear that.
I think some of the song psyches are about him as better.
Psyche songs are great.
Think what it was is that it was like random, you know, like he didn't know when he decided to Google himself one day
What you've ever been kayaking down the crazy river
Fucking I actually build a house on the crazy river did you know I've got property an acre in the geodesic dome. Yeah
Good answer three thousand square foot geodesic dome and a granny house, so what's up now?
Crazy River Beach. Very good
I got another question for you
Okay, who does number two work for?
What?
That's one of those number to work for that's one of his four jokes
Who does number two work for yes, who does number two work for?
I've no idea who I'll let you think about that one
You'll figure it out
You're a smart person
Keep it up
The boss
It's 414 the AM here. Why aren't you people asleep in bed?
Because it's only 1 14 in the AM over here. The same reason you're not the same reason you're not can't sleep, huh?
That's right. Yeah, same here. We're vampires
the
She's fun. We're having a lot of fun. Excellent can make her lipo suction surgery as well
She looks fine to me. Oh, yeah
She looked fine to me good personality good sense of humor nice lady panel, huh nice one. Yep
What are you doing over here crazy
Well, it's a pleasure talking to you folks I'm gonna be going now, you know honesty, all right
Remember I'm watching
Don't ever come back
Make sure the door doesn't hit you on the way out
SIG I'm gonna keep my eye on your son
Make sure the door doesn't hit you on the way out check your mailbox
You'll be getting a 40% discount in the upcoming week
That's crazy
All right, bye
That guy was gay. I saw him on Grindr
I know right when the next page are gonna come up. I saw that guy on Grindr. I actually
nominate
page to come up cuz she will be very refreshing tab page come up
No, oh some me
Oh my God, that says change the page, right?
That's the show?
To turn the page?
Hey, Psyche, can you kick him from studio?
Look at the crazy shit he's writing in the back.
Wow.
He's afraid to look.
Wow, Alex, that's like way beyond, bro.
Wow, that's really I want page to come up here. We need page. Hey, yes. Are you around?
Show bohola like I play my song
Sure
Tim Tim from India North cow, what up kid? What's up, bud?
That guy
NorCal I need you to tile my bathroom, bro
You guys down the pillow
Skippy the eats up all the NorCal you down to pull up. I need you to tile my bathroom
Grouch peeling out
He's right there next to you on channel NorCal
Yeah, look at the screen
You me say yeah again
Yeah
Page is here to show Bajo, and I'm excited
I'll show you my cock and I'll see your father
That everybody not here girl
not ever
we could do that somewhere else
no
we could
we could move that party somewhere else
yeah in your dream
we'll move it
like once we're tired
we're gonna move it to rumble.com
slash single sixty six
that's how you do it son
why isn't it taking all 69?
why isn't it 66?
because you can't do 66
because I've gone through several channels
because you didn't do 69
oh okay so you had to start counting down
he's bad at math
hey how are ya? what's up summer
doing good how are you sweetie
not bad just having a little insomnia
right. Welcome to the he's
thinking about all the old
at least one page freezes. It's
fucking got it in his head that
there it is. You're old joke.
What was up with that guy? NorCal NorCal promised me a discount on
Retailing and grouting my bathroom and then he know where you're gonna say NorCal. What was up with that guy?
Stale ass since a humor and his fucking delivery was horrible. What a fucking clown. Who's Sebastian. Yeah
He's always like that Bible Thumper guy very dry. I'm just one of one of my fucking
preacher man
If he was a preacher he missed the message bro. Yeah, he spoke for five six. Oh, yeah, okay
Hey, you get your ass back in bed girl. Oh, well
No, but that guy's creepy is a famous youtuber that he eats
Oh, you know, he gets like several thousand views every time it goes live. He's a white guy with long brown hair
He kind of looks like the guy from that fucking movie
Um, anyway, he's a famous youtuber that guy literally stole his fucking stick if that guy talks exactly like that
He eats old-ass food. You know what I mean? That's his that's his YouTube channel. Are you talking about Shoenice?
Shoenice didn't have any fucking air. Dude Shoenice is the is the probably the OG for doing that in all honesty
This guy and she go at each other. That's that's who are you talking about the guy in my lab
Talking about that guy talked just like him
L. A. B. Skippy a bull whatever his name is. It's true boil. It's like 62 skippy. Yeah, that's right. That's all true
Yeah, they're both they're both competitive either's but like
Shunai's got canceled because he crashes out and gets drunk on stream
I thought he quit drinking. So did I he said that several times
Would you eat a third of that?
That sounds crazy
We need to know how it's going to be like 50 bucks.
If I was shoe nice and I had the stomach that was made out of
unobtainium, yeah, sure. Who was careless of what?
Who was catered to fake misuse? Some unknown material that's indestructible. I don't know.
Who are you, J1? Right.
Is he still here? Is he still here?
Silk?
I don't know if the spider go to silk stomach or man on the right of the panel
It's light weight and it's bulletproof, so
I don't think that would work as a good stomach
I think they could make new spines out of that
Shit, really?
Can I see those seashells please?
I think there are a lot of uses that they could use for medicine
I see seashells
These shells by the seashore
show seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashells by the seashell
There she goes. There she goes.
I'm giving my own I'm giving myself my giving myself head because I have a 10-inch dick
And that's and my dick is so big that I don't get any pussy, so I have to suck my own dick
As long as you don't hate kiddies
Nobody wants to fuck me because my dick is too big
Did you hear that page? Did you hear that whole shit with ghosts?
It took a while bro. I was like what in the fucking
Wow, so I'm gonna destroy them
I'll be surprised. My husband destroyed him. He was like nah, I ain't talking to somebody that don't like cities
I'm going to bed
right
We're talking about ghosts
It's Barry's. It's you. Rest in peace, ghost. Who's in the corner? Is that
Yumi Cat? Is that baby? Uh-huh. Hi. Yeah, it's me. It's like, turn up pages, Mike. We can barely hear.
It's not really I just suck at life. It's fine. I can't I can't hear you clearly. It's better.
Is that a function?
I can show you. Well, I can go pretty good actually. I mean, I go up often. I'm not trying to downplay you. I'm trying to say that you do better.
I'm not trying to be real good. I'm just trying to learn. I'm just doing it. I'm just learning.
I got this.
I'm not good or bad. I'm just in between right now. Am I having you on more or Tiger Woods than I'm in between?
Oh, that's right.
All I said
More Bob Barker happy Gilmore twos coming out pretty soon
Rest in peace have your pet spater neuter you'll end up with fucking 2,500 cats
Did you guys
Bangin all of them municipalities will give you a ticket. He's fucking that hot one
Who's that who's that hot one with the big kids though, there was one specific
No, not Vanna white on his show. That's a different show. That was fucking whatever jeopardy or whatever fucking wheel of board
Oh, the price is right
There were three of them. There were three main ones, but there was one
with the big tits. That was the hot one.
That was Holly. There was Holly. There was Janice and there was that that third one, the hot one.
We got her name. Oh, the red. I don't know. She was a blonde. Like a dirty blonde.
I would trust, I would trust Paige's ability to breastfeed.
If you have to say that it's not true not just that summer snow
Okay, you know what fine. I'm a terrible mother. No, no, don't even say talk about your mothering people on the inner we're on the internet
I don't care. I want them to know I'm a good mom. And if they don't think so, I don't give a fuck
You're a great mom. You're great. I know I think NorCal. I think NorCal is a lame
Tyler and Grotter and that's why he won't advertise his business
Because he sucks at it
Oh, that's my opinion and her name was Diane
Now you can all go to sleep. I look like a million
I
Look like I just saved myself 150 bucks
Hey, she'll either
the
I heard said it's in the hospital. Was that a troll? Are you okay?
Yeah, I got put in the hospital
Wappy flanker said that he was gonna use he was gonna
Use a projectile device on me and on a live me
And so I was in the hospital for some time because of that. Oh
Shit, so yeah, I was in the hospital
Yeah, that guy's crazy
Yeah, that guy was crashing out on me
Like he was like, oh, I'm gonna I'm gonna put a projectile device on you and I'm gonna on the live you
Shit, I was like I've been around for a while. Yeah
Okay, he he put me in the hospital and I needed to recover for some time
I got shot, I got shot by a 22 derringer.
Cheers.
Huh?
Um, originally from the 1A community and then like a, like Vau and all that and watched
a lot of that shit like we streamed and...
The boy and all those
Why is why is
Marcy what's your version I have no aversion I have fucking shit in a kitten here right now
Okay, yeah, they were just born at five o'clock this morning. There's a little time till beans. They're so cute. That's crazy. What do you have? What do you mean?
and
you have to wait for psyche to come back this to be a
It's a little black and grey and tiger's IP.
It's a tuxedo.
Wow.
It's a pineal.
Oh.
Beebees.
Okay, look at this.
This is Mama.
Her name is Montay.
Montay.
It's a bee.
Congratulations, Mama.
She don't want to be another tuxedo.
Thank you.
She's gonna try and get away
When the babies fall asleep, you know, that's when they sneak out and chill out
And and they chill out like just just out of like
Like the babies could they can hear the baby. So like they make sure that it's the baby's scream or
fly or anything
They're so fucking cute
I showed you the one that like showed up right I think someone dropped her off. It's time ease cat. She's a himaly and I mean, yeah
Someone dropped a
Right. Well, they know that we rescue cats and work with feline network and foster kittens and shit. And I've done that for like 20 years. So
People know and I've had cats dropped off here before and this one just showed up
Just showed up
So kind of random
Are you flipping off?
I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you
Oh my god, you gotta put it in his butt and in his belly button
We'll do it at the same time
We'll do it at the same time. She's like no no thanks
I got the ditty baby oil
I
That's not too far
I'll show you too far. You want to see too far? No, I'll show you too far. I'll go too far right now
I'll shut this whole shit down right now
I know we almost shut it down earlier with all the cities on screen. Oh, that's funny
Where'd he go? Thanks for it. Yep. You got kicked because he was about to fucking pull his dick out
There's some shit
The thing about sig is he pulled his dick out before a live stream before you have to look to see it
It looks like a fucking it looks like a fucking skin
Well, the fucker was inverting I plan
That's crazy
Yeah, it is
Yeah, we did bigger clits than fucking 16
We got a fight hold on one second, I'll be right back
It's like yeah fight out on the patio. Oh
I hope it's not a skunk in the cat because that'll be a fucking night. You need to get a 22 and start
Have you guys ever heard two skunks fight? They sound like cats. It's the same.
Skunks don't make good pets. They reek.
No, they don't. They don't. You get their little stink sack taken out though and then they're apparently amazing little pets that run around their tail like this and go re-re-re-re all the time.
Are the other cats being trying to jump in there with the kittens because uh that cat will get vicious the mom
No, he's good
It's not my cat. She's my co-worker cat that lives here like the manager. We're just hanging out and having playing cards in the camper
That's not a camper. That's a double wide
Are you still on vacation?
No, I'm not. This is my work.
I'm at work. I was hanging out with my kids.
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God, you guys. My mom's birthday is today.
My mom passed away in October.
And so, like, we have to figure it out.
I'm just going through it.
So, like, we have to do something cool today.
Yeah.
Rest in peace to your mom.
Yeah, definitely.
Thank you, you know what I'm really mad at her because that bitch said she would hot the fuck out of me
And she has not lived up to it
Maybe she's busy haunting someone else right now
Stony P remember that chick that was some wild shit that chick is crazy
He mentioned moderate moderator Mike and that maybe take her
That's why I said that. Oh yeah. Yeah.
Summer. What are you doing? She ended up pregnant. Oh wait. Who ended up pregnant? Who? What? Who's pregnant?
Oh no, my co-worker's talking. Oh the cat. There's other people here yet.
Yeah, they're my co-workers cat Monte. She lives here and she's had babies. Oh, she lives there. Okay. Okay. Okay now
It's making more sense. I was like, you're at the fucking golf course in the middle of the damn night
Yes, that's what we're working on for these ones. Yeah
Somebody's got to do it, you know you made the cake for
I love them too. I feel like cats are like the final level of enlightenment on this earth, so like
You know when you're finally enlightened, that's when you get to have a life of a cat
So like I want I want to come back as one of my cats because I don't know how time and space works
You know, like it might be able to come out that way
Yeah
Maybe you should go live somewhere far away a nomadic lifestyle on your own
inside area
Marcia did you ever watch any of the CX streamers like well in a ski mask and did you ever watch ski mask Andy?
Yeah, yeah, and the car reverse and all that shit, too
Oh fucking hot mess dude. That was a real hot mess and that makes me think of immediately
That's where beta came from
Yeah
Yeah, you know she knew what the blob fish she was saying her name the other day and I was like why do I
Crystal in yeah
And I'm like
Like oh shit. That's a blob fish, right? Yeah, Crystal Anne. Yeah
That whole thing was the crazy because like
It was just such a steady decline with him, you know, and it was like over multiple years
So it was just wild. I think like that guy was a piece of shit. Sorry
He finally had a kid and he couldn't even figure it out. It's sad because some people don't don't do that
He fucking was cruel to those dogs
It was just like
Don't know I didn't see him if it was sure or not. He tried to change a lot of information that was out there
You know it was early in the
You can't
On the internet forever like yeah when Rick Pestuba got that locker and got that phone. That's where all that shit came from
that was a fucking that's true right all the stuff yeah about him and like a
underage girl right send in his proof it's pretty there's there it is that's
before people could fake shit you know I mean oh it was it happened yeah to it
yeah he did he said and the crazy part was he was like so online that he
was just lost you know it was wild it was wild to watch and I had to stop
watching it at a certain point I was like this is just sad like I can't I can't
watch this. The battle part is when Salman Andy fucking went to Aaron Carter isn't fucking
yeah that's actually how I found out a lot because of him because I'm talking to him yeah.
You know, blah, I don't want to say blossom, but you know, I'm saying yeah
He you know like he kind of like ran into him and found him and then that's what that's the first time I ever saw
Mondo was on there and then like I talked to Mondo in the background for a few years, too
He used to you know, when he was backpacking and shit. He's come through San Luis Vista County and
What can we say?
San Luis Obispo
I know where that's at
So I'm Louie born and raised baby. Yep
Yeah, that's in the Bay Area
Music company that makes bases there music man bases St. Louis. It's a beautiful place actually. Yeah
Yeah, there's a lot of really cool stuff like I like it here, you know growing up here
It was always like oh, there's nothing to do there was nothing to do
But then after you like grow up and see the world and want to like settle down and shit
I'm like, oh, I'm so glad that like our family bought this property because me and my husband were able to come and help my mom
Pay the mortgage off and like it's the family property now, you know like
And you guys have some land there a little over an acre. Yeah, but that's what that's what I have here
It's rule, you know, everybody around us has an acre and we're I mean, there's only a couple stores in town
So I'll through send respect this boy. I'm used to work out there
I'm in the last town. Let's just say that and then let's just look down
so
Where the red-headed stepchild
You can't really do it
Dude, that's so gnarly. I'm sorry you went through that dude. My mom didn't marry until after my dad passed away
And I was 20 already
Right and brings you to who you are today, you know, um, sorry, I couldn't hear you nor Cal what?
I'm reading the chat and talking to the chair
Yeah, crazy
Lion lion one
Hey, it's crazy, huh? We've lost so many people from the one day like in the last five six years
What's the way what does that mean?
Like the first I'm in mid cop watch, you know like the auditor
Formerly auditor like to call activists nowadays, you know
Yeah
Chat, you know the Vegas chat and wherever we're all those type of people
Like
Casey wasn't she part of that?
Who?
See why
Not that I know I don't know you. I was talking to KT in chat. Oh
What
I'm pretty sure she got an abortion
He's got an abortion. I had an abortion when I was 19
I've never had an abortion or a pregnancy scare. I didn't think I, I actually have a, I can't, I'm not supposed to be able to have kids and then I had Grace and I was like, boom.
And she almost killed me.
I was with my ex-husband. I was with my ex-husband actually and like I was on birth control.
So it was a fucking surprise.
The kid would look like Dobby.
I can't imagine if I have a kid with my ex-husband, the way that like his family was, holy shit.
I'm so glad.
I mean, I definitely made the right choice for me and him at that time, so, but it sucked.
I mean, it wasn't something we wanted to do.
We were on birth control, you know?
We weren't planning on having a kid for a long time or for at least longer than I was 19,
you know?
Never ended up having kids with him. We split up and I'm my husband and we've been married for 17 years, so
Rock-n-roll, baby. Oh, we got a beautiful 16 year old daughter
It's pretty cool, and I have a 19 year old stepdaughter. I
Can't believe she's 19. That's crazy to me
She was young
This is the first time I've been on streamers in several months. It's all changed the format's different
It's just in the last few days that it's changed because like I noticed that too
Like maybe it was in the last week with Tommy Jones. Thank you
What did she even say
I don't know
Tommy Jones cuz I'm not looking to breed there is a chat read chat. Oh, oh, there's a simp and chat. Let me see. Oh
Imagine that chat back chat shit you
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh my God.
That's so gross.
The fucked up way of describing a redheaded ginger's man's penis?
Yes, accurate, exactly.
I don't think I've ever been with a ginger.
Been to what, Virginia?
Well, I guess my ex-husband kind of was a ginger.
My ex-husband kind of was a ginger. He like had like blonde hair
But like when he his beard grew out or his stuff or whatever would grow out. It was red
So I think he had ginger. Well, his uncle would definitely had it in
But
Now I prefer to mate with her or have sex with people with souls mate like I'm an animal
He's an animal of sorts
What do you do page? What do you what do you do the golf course different things? Do you ever drive the car around with beer?
Did you fever is I have this?
Yes
I mean the golf course
Oh
You know the golf course you graduate of lawnmowers
Yeah, we do everything everybody has their all the jobs here. It's not just like one person
Usually there's groundskeepers they call up the people that keep the ground
We do it all
Is it a part what? Is it a league style course? A league style course?
It means that the holes are linked together.
It's an ATL course. Yes, it's an ATL course. Front nine, front and back front nine. Yes.
I got you.
you because if you hit up into the other fairway, you can go over and hit your ball out of it without taking a penalty.
But anyway, it depends on how you play because like yes and no.
I mean if you want to play that way, I mean I prefer like
and I'm definitely not going to play it on that court.
All I mean is if you hit it somewhere, it's not out of bounds like because there'll be a marker to mark if your ball's out of bounds.
Well, I found them out of bounds.
Yes, I do.
I'm not trying to dox your golf course.
I was just trying to check it out.
No, no, no, it's okay.
But yes, if I get it out, but personally, I think it's a personal thing, right?
Like, it's however you want to fucking play, because no one's out there monitoring how
you play and what you call, right?
It's just you and whoever you're playing with.
Like I told her, one day I will show...
I like to play appropriately, though, so if I get out into the next fucking, if I'm
Well, if you hit it on a green in a different fairway, that's out of balance because you
can't hit like an iron or anything from there.
If I get it on another green though, I'll be like, hey, I'm playing that.
I got what you're saying.
You're just going to do whatever I got you.
Okay, get this so like mind you I play like after work every day no one's out here
So I have to yell for like go play until dark. We do every night rain or shine, but
But I fucking if we're playing and we're playing with a bunch of people and we keep it
Like actual act like accuracy to it and you're playing for points then it kind of changes it, right?
It depends on who you're playing with and what you're doing.
So if I come out here on my day off, which I do every fucking time, I'm always here.
And then if I'm playing with a bunch of people who are very mortally etiquette, professional, that kind of thing, then yes.
But if not, and we're just playing for fun, then the fuck it is a free-for-all.
I gotcha.
Yeah.
I also have a little bit more play because I work here, right?
So like we can fuck with carts and we can fuck with this like we have a little bit more wiggle room
Carts, doesn't really sad man, carts
I'd be like whatever about the golf. Let's take part. I've played some pretty nice
I've had the luck. I've been lucky enough to play some nice golf courses
We have a lot now here like just in like our local area
Have some beautiful courses especially in Montana and shit like that. Fuck. Yeah, California. You guys are beautiful. Yeah
Well, I'm crazy here, but I played pebble beach before
You know the famous golf course pebble beach. I've played that before it was 500 bucks
I got you
Dude this town the town that I worked for this golf course for which is like I live in a mill in nowhere
So every town is like kind of my town that's in the surrounding area
But this one is like fucking like a village. It's not even it's not even a town to a village. So
That sounds like
It is members only but there was a
Fundraiser and that's how you get it's a to raise funds. So they let
You know a group of people
Large group of people play it to raise the money for whatever money that they they donated
So that's all the time
Honestly we do some charity work too am I like
It goes to a good cause always I love that you're awesome. You're awesome
No, I didn't do charity work
I'm saying that I gave 500 bucks to play this you know exquisite golf course the same as golf course
We got lucky enough to do it. I played a boot from Donald Trump golf courses, too
Yeah, I ain't no kind of members only kind guy. I got that kind of money country glad that that's for
That's for
Page look in the back chat. I put
Like my area you look up the golf courses because it basically this area is like
Retiree area now because it's expensive and shit or a vacation area
So there's a lot of golf courses and shit around here. Oh
Classy sassy. Good morning cowgirl. Yee-haw. How are you girl? No, I'm
San Luis Vismo is a rich people town
That's wild. I'm glad my parents love property because otherwise I would have been fucking elses
No, like it's kind of more like a lot of them around here too. Like especially the swankier ones
It's like snow birds, you know, I mean they come like I live here in Canada this time of year
And I live in Arizona this time of year those kind of people, right?
and or rich old people like it's it's very much it there's either young people or older people
there's an in between but not really you know i mean like it's hard for families right like
you definitely have to bring 10 fucking kids out there i mean like let's go golfing
golf is not a poor people sport it's right no it's for people that that are you know i mean
get the clubs, if you get good ones, they're expensive,
and to go play good places is expensive.
So that's where I guess we differ,
because we're a little bit more affordable.
And it's more laid back here than anywhere else
I've ever been, but at the same time,
it's also still a challenging fucking course.
It's not easy to play, but it's beef and it's fun.
It's under the poverty line or just above people
They need to figure it out like that. It's better for the country or for people to be
Successful and have a middle class
Right
Fuck dude, I couldn't imagine any time we were gopping we were just outside to fuck around and have a good time, you know
So, like, it might be my plan.
The only reason I ask is, well, he really fucking,
there's certain things that he, like, drilled into my head
about golf that now I teach other people here.
And I'm, like, blindly in the blind kind of,
but I'll say no one talk about it.
It always works.
Right?
Like, I guess I learned it.
That's not everything happens for a reason, right?
You know, he didn't.
He got fucked.
Knowledge is good, I guess, whatever.
All those lessons, all that shit,
gets you to where you are now.
So how can you knock it, right?
like it is what it is
gotta do what you gotta do baby
yeah christ isn't asleep that's what i was gonna say christ is asleep
You should be waking up soon though, right?
Thank you, I grew myself like I always say, you know
My back carry these bitches around, but hey
God bless modern medicine
You know like it's one of those things though
I watched a girl run across the road one time by a 7-Eleven and her boobs were so big I stewed blackening both her fucking eyes.
That's what I was gonna say. Yeah, if you don't have a good sports bra and you run like you usually have to hold on
Otherwise, there's just too much, you know, like you should have seen when I was breastfeeding. Oh my god
Like what size everything we're like proportionally adequate to what we're supposed to be, right? Yeah, I
wear a size nine shoe like
My dad always used to say
That makes sense though. That's personally fine. That's adequate because it's balanced.
The women on my dad's side of the family, we are all big breasted, right? And my dad said
we all have big feet and it's because like, you know, like a clown, like when you push it over
but because it has big shoes, it doesn't fall over and stand back up. That's the whole thing.
So we don't fall forward on our faces. We got the big feet, right?
I don't have any bad nymphs. I'm too close to the ground to be necessary for that.
How tall are you?
I can hear him now.
Was that 5'1"? Is that what you said?
God, you and Summer are like the same height. That's wild!
Like a
My my daughter is she's gonna be 16 right in a month and she she's five three and then like still growing
So my daughter is literally like the same size as me and growing and she just looks at me like bitch
What's you gonna do?
You should have seen like before my neck got fixed like I was the same way to my daughter
Hold on a second she
It's it's Paige. She's at work and there's people around her. There's a guy talking next to her
But that's what the men for the man's voice you hear is
Yeah, she's at work. So I'm not working anymore. Oh
I still hear somebody talking here. Yeah, she's hanging out. There's people around.
Because I'm at my work hanging out with my co-workers that are still here.
No, no, okay.
In chat, they're talking about...
In chat, they hear the talking in the background.
They thought it was Chris.
And that's why I said no Chris in the sleep.
Yeah, so...
No, it's my co-worker.
You know who LA beast is the youtuber
Skippy whatever that guy that was on panel earlier that had that fucking delivery that weird talks that he was doing
That's that's his voice. He was trying it that he stole ripped off that guy talks exactly like that. He was a fucking thief
An unoriginal thief
Risma no fucking nothing that guy
Trying to get up there, but the panel was full I wanted to talk to him because I wanted to tell him about himself as far as
His stick goes and it was fucking rotten the guy was gonna fucking creep
He's saying some stupid not one joke was funny. He had nothing not even
Something that made me smile. All it did is made me cring
That was only a year ago, she was 14 at the time.
My daughter might have dropped on her a year ago.
It was kind of funny though.
KK and me had this beef for whatever reason going back and forth for a little bit and like
No KT in the chat. Oh, and like we both been mods on a lot of 1a pages together
And we had no problems and then I don't know it's some people kind of got in and like disrupted shit and
whatever like
Anyway, so people take this way too serious. They don't realize you got on the panel and was talking
Well, I was on a lot of medication like when my neck was broken obviously
And I would take my muscle relaxer and be on these panels and pass out and I wouldn't turn my camera off
So it wasn't a good look, you know, but it wasn't anything nefarious like I'm not doing dope
I'm not like overtaking medication. It does. It's not cute like it's something that I haven't done in a long time now, but
For whatever the case she was saying that it made me a bad mom even though my daughter was already in bed asleep
Right when I was on the panel
Um, and my daughter came out and I was like if you want to ask her ask her
Ask her how she feels about it and she talked to her my daughter talked to her for a minute
I came in went to the bathroom came back out and
My daughter was like well
If you had a problem with it, you're the one that's a 56 year old woman yelling at a 14 year old bitch and then handed me the headphones back
So it just was what it was. Well, she was saying, oh my god, you're 12 year old daughters
Well, we'll just listen
Leave the kids alone meaning don't ever bring your kid anywhere near any of these fucking places. There's some of the most
Generous
Motherfuckers that you'll ever come across
I learned a lot in the last couple of years on these panels and shit fucking shit. This shit's fucking demonic
Yeah, there's demons in here, you know
Phone every day
What do you say page
Anyway, um, yeah, my daughter's a teenager and she knows you know, like
Like we have open communication. So that's kind of like what it was, you know
Because I don't really know offense, but uh
This is the internet. You don't have to prove nothing to nobody here. You don't know these yeah, I know
And you know, it's funny though is like
And people have tried to drag my name and like say shit about me. That's not true or like lie or whatever
Ignore it and I can't even see it. That's the whole thing. I just have to laugh at it now because it's kind of crazy
Yeah, I was gonna jump down to I love you page
No, you're gay, Katie. I don't know you either. No, that's that's a good point. I got you but
You don't want people near them, but not children. Yeah, but that was the whole thing
My daughter wasn't around, you know, she had already gone to bed like when I was getting on the panel
Yeah, but you woke her up to prove a point. Is it what I'm at? No, no, no, she wasn't she was awake that day
That was like all those people are on the East Coast, you know, and that was earlier and in the
evening it was like
True points to people on the internet with
Fucking you know waking people up and waking kids up and shit. Yeah. No, that's not what happened or some shit
Which I know behavior while it was like she came out to ask me if she could have
Something some ice cream or some fucking shit and and like it just happened at the right time. She's like, why are you?
Upset. What are you talking to this person online? I was like, oh, she's
Dragging me for falling asleep on panel, you know without turning the camera off
And she was saying that I wasn't a good mom for doing that.
My daughter was already asleep, you know, so I didn't I mean obviously, it's not a good book like I learned
I saw it was played back for myself Katie played a bunch of things for me
And she really opened my eyes to falling asleep while the camera was on to make me sure that I just
In the chat, right? Yeah. Yeah
They're cool now and you said thank you for you know trying to help me, but I didn't see it
Time but I didn't yeah at the time right and and yeah, like it's water under the bridge at this point
Should be I mean it sounds like they were trying to give you some good advice or constructive criticism or when you're talking about
That was my foster daughter and she was two years older than Bella Donna. So she's actually
Almost done with her credits now at high school and she's going to graduate early
So she's doing really good, but she had to go to a boarding school
I know this one lady that
There's only so much you can do as a foster parent especially in California like it's really
It's frustrating to try and be a parent and have rules and things but then have like to stay undermine you
As a parent, so she was online. She was doing things, but she wasn't
She was doing talking to people and doing all that way
To adults. She's talking about my foster daughter
To adults on the internet. She was talking to my friends. Yeah
Yeah, but not all the time and not usually without me supervising so
Not that I know she only came on my streams. So I didn't know you streamed
Yeah, I I did panels
Hopefully you uh, but I had a broken neck at the time I had a lot of shit going on
I took on a foster daughter to you at that time she
She had run away from a group home or whatever we
I don't need to go into it too much
She needed a more secure, kind of lockdown type of system for her, so.
I got you.
She didn't and she thrived ever since.
So there's two.
Still on our phone plan.
We still talk through all the lines.
There's still some angst between you and KT.
I'm from my observation, which is right now.
You know nothing.
I didn't know anything about this.
Yeah.
You know, it's water under the bridge. You say now, but there's still some animosity. I can I can sense it
You know, but it is
I'm more like upset that I'm still getting trolled by like some of the people that caused the the issue between
Myself and Katie and other people, you know
And they're still in this chat right here. So
It's just annoying. Like I wish that people would just kind of like go on with their lives and
Point it's your fault the reason why I'm so I'm not I'm just and this is all just
You're still feeding the energy that the people are giving you back from that how many years ago it was
So what I'm saying is
You got you at this point you got to ignore that you can't keep
People cannot let go of some fucking shit. They just can't they keep saying the same thing like that guy earlier
That guy earlier they're saying oh he time me out
You know like you find out that people sit there and talk about someone timing you out for five minutes forever
Exactly, exactly. Wow
Who who was that again? I forgot it was crying
I don't remember
Sebastian I'm guessing oh fuck that guy that guy deserves to be banned
Exile
Don't know him, but he was annoying
We knew him and we got our first impressions are very strong and that guy was fucking off
Weird what a weird guy fucking coming up here fucking quote fucking shit. Yeah, but movies and shit fucking God knows
What a weirdo true Katie like Katie and I have known a lot of each other for a long time on here
so I'm glad that like she and I are at a point where we're all right with each other and
All that you know is water under the bridge and then we figured I figured out finally how to take her off of my block list
Ct yeah, there was a shit show for a couple months there, but how long ago
Um, that was a little over a year ago, maybe
Ten years in real life
Yeah, it was a lot was going on a lot was going on at that time, but
We got you in your feelings. Yeah, I know me too, but I think like
Yeah, that's what it was at heart and it was hard for me because I saw a problem with it as well, you know, Casey, that was what the whole thing was.
So it's frustrating, but we go through things and like Paige said, you know, coming out the other side is what fucking matters, right?
So it's crazy though. I can't believe it.
Doing so well because she was at like a year behind in school when she went up there and she just
Fostered a child that that's yeah, that's pretty gracious
Yeah, she kind of appeared on the doorstep and just like that cat
Yeah
She bought my daughter home the
Skate park and she didn't have anywhere to stay and she had
An adult man offering her a hotel room, and I was like, no
And I actually went through all the training to become a licensed foster care parent and all that
Oh, well dealing with a broken neck and doing I had to do all the 36 hours of training
A whole bunch of shit. Well, I had this issues
and it was it got dislocated and I got an injection and it gave me an
infection which started to eat away at the bone and then I went for another
injection about two months later and they overdosed me on the table and had
the narcomia and when they flipped me over I don't know what happened but
right after that my hands started going numb
And then like over a four month period,
I lost the use of my legs and my hands and my arms
and I couldn't, and I was basically paralyzed.
I had-
Did you get meningitis?
No, it was an infection from whatever
in the injection they gave me.
It started to eat away at the bone.
And so when they pulled me off the table,
when they overdosed me,
they pulled me in such a way that it like broke my neck,
It took that time to kind of keep sliding like over that four months, you know
So when they broke it, it made it so that my hands like mostly just like this hand on this side at first
And then I lost this hand
This one and then yeah, and then about like in that was at the end of April and then by September
I was paralyzed and ended up I went to the hospital
Um, they did a cat pan and they said your neck is broken and dislocated and we can't help you here
So they had to take me down to LA to Northridge. There was a doctor there. They knew that they did good job doing neck surgery
Um, I had a what consider his spinal cord injury. So
It was fucking gnarly dude. Like it was the craziest. I didn't know that you could break your neck and still live
like
Oh, you can
You can't oh, yeah, I know I did it. I did it. So this is a here people to get severe whip last break their neck to sometimes so
Damn, it's so small. I don't know if you can see that would I can let me see I can't I was in the chat
x-ray
You know, it's ironic side-by-side that in the chat earlier show x-ray
Well, that's funny an hour or so ago. I typed in the chat just show your x-ray
Oh, yeah, yeah, I typed that it's funny. Yeah, that's the x-ray from broken neck. That's the two side-by-side
Yeah, that's
It's too small I think like it without being full screen, but this is the surgery that they did I have four cages and
All those screws going up and down
I know you can see that that's all the metal in my neck. That's my neck now. So it's straight now
You know, it was like basically like my head was on my shoulder almost like I was holding a house phone
You know like all the time
So that was a crazy thing looking at any of those old streams like it's hard for me because I'm like, oh my god
my neck was fucked, you know, but
Like I streamed that night after coming home from when they had overdosed me
Made a bruise on my chest right here from them trying to bring me back and gradually just lost the hands, you know
Okay, I'm glad you're doing better. Hell. Yeah, me too
Resilience resilience and God seriously, I don't think I could have made it without
It's also the survival of the fittest, you know, such kind of thing exactly
I'm a Leo just like COVID. I mean these people that I know that that died from COVID
Yeah, yeah, that were a good friend. I mean completely healthy
Yeah
Yeah, it's wild that shit was wild. I had a good friend
Who lost his older brother his dad and his little sister?
All in the same month like his older brother had had COVID and was put on a ventilator in December and
By January like all three of those people in his family
And that's a man. It was a man. It's man-made. It's not a natural. No
So
Somebody who was so selfish that they were like, I'm gonna put this out
Into the world because I've only can get so far in a lab doing my testing
You know and that's the fuck part, but they were like we're gonna kill a bunch of people and see what happens
You know, well, they knew if you it's not like that. They knew what was gonna happen
It's not just
I watched the the scientist going in front of Congress when was that like a couple of years ago
2023, I think?
Yeah, talking about it. All that stuff is staged out a little bit too, so the real stuff happens.
Not me, but it used to happen on the internet where you could see where people would take information from places.
that they did and they would take it and share it privately where you couldn't get in and see what they were looking at.
I see chats and shit like back in the day.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Every Clinton's email, her server, her private servers and shit.
No, her, yeah, everything was taken out of it.
The Benghazi?
What the Benghazi stuff is that what you're talking about every single thing the wiki leeks and
All of it do you think that they fucking melted Julian Assange his brain like medically?
Oh, he was so fucking sharp and then like he basically is like when he came back, you know, he's just a
Former shell of his old self. You know, it's just weird
Well, I mean get to weird on site shower. I want to get it
You know what we're talking about
Like we were to talk about you know what happened in New York a long time ago
Yeah, yeah, I mean listen the elevator retrofitting you mean
I've seen all that stuff
That's about that. That's crazy, right
Wild stuff, you know, it's literally, you know, like the matrix you take the blue or the red pill, you know
And I'm trying to like the rest of your life knowing that that's what's going on in the world
I'm trying to learn like a manifestation
Because I think that the manifestation I'm trying to learn how to manifest and use consciousness and collective consciousness
And you know like that kind of shit and see how that all can work to change the world
I think it'd be a very interesting
You know, I just I just started looking into it. So I don't know all about it yet
But you know, you think that uh, you know, the country is divided politically by happenstance. I
Think people are fooled. No, no, no, no
No, not everybody can pick up on it. They're gonna get what yeah, that's true. What I'm saying. Yeah, it's the indoctrination
Do you think there is a do you think that that's by design like that? Oh, yeah
Education and all that
Keeping everybody divided keeping groups like those people hate those people because they
You know purpose that isn't just some and they're all together doing it separately with the other which is you know United corporations of America
That's crazy.
Right?
Everybody over there fucking standing and lying trying to vote.
That's the biggest fucking shit show I've ever seen.
I voted.
Well, are you wasting your time?
It's just your time none of that. It's all predetermined
The sad part is is that like they think there's a big group of people that doesn't want change and I love our larger group of people
But how do we take that power back?
Have you ever seen there's a movie on Netflix it's called the square have you ever seen it?
This I don't think that's the name of the movie. It's a Netflix. It's a it's a documentary. Oh
Yeah, it's called this when you get some time when you get some time watch it because that's how it's gonna happen
That's how it would have to happen. It would be like just like that exactly like that
That's what it would look like if we were to do that in our country
So there's an outline you can watch it and that's how it would have to happen. It'll never happen here
Yeah, I'm more like thinking about all the volcanoes and shit that are exploding and what happens if Yellowstone burst and all that
I'm like, all the animals are leaving Yellowstone
Well, this is not a good time, bro. Like I don't like that. I don't like that
but
I don't know. I also like I'm a believer like I'm a very spiritual person
like I think that there is a higher power and there is a larger purpose and
This is just one part of our our soul or human
You know body is just one part of our existence
Not even on earth. I mean living on earth and a human body is just one part of our souls experience, you know
So because we're all it's energy, right? Energy can't be destroyed. It just changes form. So
you know, that's why I feel like the matrix isn't too far off from exactly what's happening. It's very
close to the Coen brothers and you know, it's like it's kind of like that. It's actually kind of like
Things yeah, yep. Have you ever done DMT? No, I haven't okay. That's an interesting one
I haven't tried it before
That is I've studied that, you know, right? Yeah, I've looked a lot into it
Yeah, it's interesting because it's an every living thing right like it exists
So what chemical yeah exactly?
Yeah
Almost like the cannabinoid receptors in your brain, right?
And marijuana just happens to grow all over the world. What a surprise morning, man
Oh man, anyway, I probably should go to sleep. Yeah, me too. It was nice talking to you. Yeah, good talking to you NorCal.
You take care of yourself. All right, you too. Bye-bye. Good night. Good night chat. Everybody stay free.